我是一个多愁善感的笨蛋，仅此而已
♪ I'm a sentimental sap, that's all ♪
♬努力不跌倒有什么用?♪
♪ What's the use of trying not to fall? ♪
♪我没有意志，你已经让你灭了♪
♪ I have no will, you've made your kill ♪
因为你占了我的便宜
♪ 'Cause you took advantage of me ♪
♪我就像树枝上的苹果♪
♪ I'm just like an apple on a bough ♪
♬你要想办法把我甩掉♬
♪ And you're going To shake me down somehow ♪
但是有什么用呢?你把我的鹅给毁了
♪ But what's the use? You've cooked my goose ♪
因为你占了我的便宜
♪ 'Cause you took advantage of me ♪
我是如此的性感和烦恼以至于我不知道
♪ I'm so hot and bothered That I don't know ♪
♬我的手肘从我的耳朵♬
♪ My elbow from my ear ♪
♬每次你走，我都承受着可怕的痛苦
♪ I suffer something awful Each time you go ♪
当你靠近♬时，情况会更糟
♪ It's much worse when you're near ♪
♬我在这里，我所有的桥都被烧毁了♬
♪ Here am I With all my bridges burned ♪
♪只是你怀里的一个宝贝
♪ Just a babe in arms Where you're concerned ♪
♬所以锁好门，叫我你的
♪ So lock the doors and call me yours ♪
因为你占了我的便宜
♪ 'Cause you took advantage of me ♪
♪我没有意志，你已经让你灭了♪
♪ I have no will, you've made your kill ♪
因为你占了我的便宜
♪ 'Cause you took advantage of me ♪
♬所以把门锁上
♪ So lock the doors ♪
♬我是你的
♪ And call me yours ♪
♬你占了便宜
♪ You took advantage ♪
♪可怜的小我♪
♪ Of poor little me ♪
弩，我是看门狗。
Crossbow, this is Watchdog.
确认鉴别器上的所有传送。
Confirm all transmissions on Discriminator.
收到,看门狗
Roger, Watchdog.
十字弓启动鉴别器，所有系统就绪。
Crossbow is on Discriminator, and all systems are go.
收到，我们指示你进入机动程序。
Roger, we mark you go for maneuvering sequence.
看门狗，我是十字弓。
Watchdog, this is Crossbow.
我建立了。确认我们准备发射武器。
I am established. Confirm we are go for arm.
收到,十字弓
Affirmative, Crossbow.
选择电器到最大，通风口打开和系统到板上。
Select electrics to max, vents to open and systems to onboard.
——收到。十字弓准备完毕。——收到。
- Roger. Crossbow is armed. - Roger.
我们现在得到地面确认。兔子在洞里。
We now have ground confirmation. Rabbit is in the hole.
移动目标指示器，开火。
Moving Target Indicator, engage.
探路者。我要上瞄准镜了。
Pathfinder is on. I'm going on the scope.
收到。
Roger.
开启扫描仪。
Scanner on.
目标锁定。跟踪锁定。
Target locked. Tracking locked.
——收到。-慢慢来。就是这样。
- Roger. - Easy does it. That's it.
就在那儿别动。
Hold it right there.
弩项目。
The Crossbow Project.
好的进攻是最好的防守。
There's no defense like a good offense.
任务完成
Mission accomplished.
——突出,弩。-就像在桶里打鸭子。
- Outstanding, Crossbow. - Just like shooting ducks in a barrel.
在秘密的工作中，我们的科学家正在把一个工程梦想变成有效的现实。
Working in secret, our scientists are turning an engineering dream into an effective reality.
-现在我们要做的就是建造它。-不错的小武器，对吧，戴夫?
- Now all we have to do is build it. - Nice little weapon, isn't it, Dave?
罗伊，你觉得唐的电影怎么样?
What do you think of Don's movie, Roy?
我觉得里面的女孩不够多。
I think there weren't enough girls in it.
我有一卷关于其他武器用途的带子，小型航天飞机计划，以及用于空中发射的B-1改装。
Well, I have a little tape on alternate weapon uses, mini-shuttle plans, and B-1 modifications for aerial launch.
总统或任何其他负责机构知道此事吗?
Does the president or any other responsible agency know about this?
这是机密，乔治。再说了，这是中情局的责任。
We're on a need-to-know basis, George. Besides, the CIA's responsible.
我觉得他们确实需要知道。你会导致事态升级的。
I think they do need to know. You're gonna cause a major escalation.
我们的研究表明，这种武器在战争中完全无用。
Our studies indicate that this type of weapon is totally useless in warfare.
它不适合用在你的战争中。
It's not intended for use in your kind of warfare.
这是和平时期最完美的武器。这就是为什么它是秘密。
It's the perfect peacetime weapon. That's why it's secret.
-所以这既不道德又不道德?——是的。
- So it's both immoral and unethical? - Yes.
我们什么时候能拿到?
When do we get it?
据我所知，能源似乎有一个小的技术问题——我不想听到任何问题。我们计划今年夏天卖掉你的枪。
As I understand it, there seems to be a small technical problem with the energy source-- I don't want to hear about any problems. We have plans for your gun this summer.
我需要在这里取得成功。
I need a success here.
我不希望任何延误影响到我们的成功。
I don't need any delays jeopardizing that success.
-我说的够清楚了吗，唐?——哦。清晰的伏特加。
- Am I making myself clear, Don? - Oh. Clear as vodka.
你叫那个海瑟薇医生给我坐下。
You tell that Dr. Hathaway to get on the stick.
-那我得更用力了。-只要我们六月前有武器就行。
- I'm gonna have to push harder, then. - As long as we have a weapon by June.
——对,将军?-我不知道，戴夫。
- Right, general? - I wouldn't know, Dave.
自从朝鲜战争后我就没有能用的武器了。
I haven't had a working weapon since Korea.
我很抱歉,大卫。这太过分了。
I'm sorry, Dave. This is too much.
-我要申请调任-很遗憾听到这个消息，乔治。
- I'm gonna ask for reassignment. - Sorry to hear that, George.
我强烈要求你停止。
I urge you to stop.
谢谢你的建议。很遗憾你不能加入球队。
Thanks for your input. Sorry you won't be on the team.
也许下次。
Maybe next time.
太糟糕了。以前是个好人。
Too bad. Used to be a good man.
恐怕我们得解放乔治了。
I'm afraid we're gonna have to liberate George.
解放?你的意思是,清算?
Liberate? You mean, liquidate?
拉里，我们去看那部关于致盲技术的电影。
Larry, let's see that film on blinding techniques.
然后我们一起吃午饭。
Then we'll all have some lunch.
-你能签这个吗?-你是海瑟薇博士吗?
- Could you sign this, please? - Are you Dr. Hathaway?
是的,我是。
Yes, I am.
我很喜欢你的电视节目。
I just loved your television show.
非常感谢。你真是太好了。
Thank you very much. That's very kind of you.
听。告诉我，爱因斯坦先生到底是什么样的人?
Listen. Tell me, uh, what is Mr. Einstein really like?
死了。
Dead.
你看，爸爸，激光是指通过刺激辐射来放大光。
See, Dad, laser means light amplification by stimulated emissions of radiation.
这是相干光。
So this is coherent light.
——哦。它会说话，对吧?——没有。
- Oh. So it talks, right? - No.
-海瑟薇博士，真是个惊喜!-你好吗，泰勒夫人?
- Dr. Hathaway, what a surprise! - How are you, Mrs. Taylor?
米奇的考试成绩有问题吗?
Something wrong with Mitch's test scores?
如果有，那是因为我感冒了不能给他做早餐。
If there is, it's because I had the flu and couldn't make him breakfast.
我想我应该飞过来亲自告诉你这个消息。
Well, I thought I'd fly in and bring you the news myself.
我刚从招生处得到消息。我们做到了。米奇在太平洋理工大学。
I just got word from Admissions. We did it. Mitch is in at Pacific Tech.
-这不是很好吗?-干得好，小子!
- Isn't that wonderful? - Way to go, boy!
别摇他的头!
Don't shake his head!
-你好吗，米奇?——好。
- How you doing, Mitch? - Fine.
-这里陈列得不错。——谢谢。
- Nice display here. - Thanks.
这是一种342纳米的闪光灯泵浦紫外线激光。
It's a flash-lamp-pumped ultraviolet laser at 342 nanometers.
如你所知，人们对核聚变用的原子碘激光很感兴趣。
Well, as you know, there is interest in the atomic iodine laser for fusion.
这是分子碘。
This is molecular iodine.
因此，这种激光不受原子碘的复合影响。
Therefore, this laser doesn't suffer from recombination of the atomic iodine.
你一定很自豪。
You must be very proud.
——骄傲?-哦,是的。确定。
- Proud? - Oh, yeah. Sure.
米奇是我们冬至学期接收的第一个学生。
Mitch is the first student we've ever accepted for midwinter term.
——亲爱的。-我想他也是最小的。
- Honey. - I imagine he's the youngest too.
不。事实上，我们最小的孩子才12岁。
No. Actually, the youngest we ever had was 12.
他在压力下不到六个月就崩溃了。
He cracked under the pressure within six months.
米奇是15。这不会有任何问题的。
Mitch is 15. There's not gonna be any problem with that.
正确的。听着，博士，关于奖学金的事。
Right. Listen, doc, about this scholarship thing.
你会给他签约奖金，对吧?
Now, you're gonna give him a signing bonus, right?
不。但是通过让米奇加速进步，我们给了他机会去实现他的潜能。
No. But by allowing Mitch to progress at an accelerated rate, we give him the opportunity to fulfill a far greater portion of his potential.
我们只是想给米琪最好的。
We just want the best for Mitchie.
海瑟薇博士，我那天晚上看了你关于放射性同位素的节目。
Dr. Hathaway, I saw your show the other night on radioactive isotopes.
-我有个问题要问你。——是吗?
- And I've got a question for you. - Yes?
-那是你的真头发吗?-是的。
- Is that your real hair? - Yeah.
-告诉我，米奇是领养的吗?——为什么,不!
- Tell me, is Mitch by any chance adopted? - Why, no!
——这是惊人的。——不是吗?
- It's amazing. - Isn't it?
如果我不吃点东西，我会死的。
If I don't get something to eat, I'm gonna die.
-再见，海瑟薇医生。——再见。
- Bye, Dr. Hathaway. - Goodbye.
回头见，亲爱的。
I'll see you later, honey.
他们真的很好。
They're really all right.
只是有时候他们不知道我在说什么。
It's just sometimes they don't know what I'm talking about.
我很确定。告诉我，米奇，你会想念你的朋友吗?
I'm sure about that. So tell me, Mitch, are you gonna miss your friends?
-不，我觉得我吓到其他孩子了。——好男孩。
- No, I think I intimidate other kids. - Good boy.
米奇，有件事你得明白。
Mitch, there's something you're going to have to understand.
和你相比，大多数人的智商和胡萝卜差不多。
Compared to you, most people have the IQ of a carrot.
我们和大多数人不一样，米奇。更好。我-你在这啊，海瑟薇医生!-嗨。好的，稍等，稍等。
We're different than most people, Mitch. Better. I'm-- - There you are, Dr. Hathaway! - Hi. Yes, one second, one second.
我把你安排进了我自己的研究小组里面有全校最优秀的人才。
I've put you on my own research team with the finest minds on the campus.
这是我第二次把这样的荣誉授予新生。
This is the second time I've ever given such an honor to a freshman.
第一个是1981年的克里斯·奈特，对吧?
The first one was Chris Knight in 1981, right?
-你听说过克里斯吗?-是的，他是物理学的传奇人物。
- You've heard of Chris? - Yes, he's a physics legend.
你将和克里斯一起工作。
You're going to be working with Chris.
他现在大四了，他和以前一样聪明。
He's a senior now, and he's as brilliant as he ever was.
哇。
Wow.
你一毕业，这份工作就等着你了，克里斯。
Soon as you graduate, this job will be waiting, Chris.
太好了。
Great.
我们在这里有一个完整的实体工厂。-你有按摩浴缸?
- We have a complete physical plant here. - You have a Jacuzzi?
——当然。——好。
- Absolutely. - Good.
实验室和办公室就在这边。
And the labs and offices are right over this way.
请跟我来。
Follow me, please.
伙计们!
Guys!
-来见见克里斯·奈特。我是雪莉·努吉尔。-很高兴见到你。
- Meet Chris Knight. This is Sherry Nugil. - Pleased to meet you.
-这位是迈克·多德。——多德博士?
- And this is Mike Dodd. - Dr. Dodd?
他刚刚设计了我们全新的电信卫星。
The one who just designed our brand-new Telcom satellite.
很荣幸见到您，先生。
It's an honor to meet you, sir.
电信产品。
Telcom.
那颗卫星不就是把碎片撒遍欧洲的卫星吗?
Isn't that the satellite that's raining debris all over Europe?
为什么那个玩具在你头上?
Why is that toy on your head?
因为如果我把它穿到别的地方，它就会摩擦。
Because if I wear it anywhere else, it chafes.
我很抱歉。我只是不想让你们觉得我很古板。
I'm sorry. It's just that I didn't want you guys to think I was stuffy.
你知道，没有乐趣。只有大脑，没有阴茎。
You know, no fun. All brain, no penis.
——原谅我?——我很抱歉。
- Pardon me? - I'm sorry.
这只是对权威的幼稚反应。
It's just an infantile response to authority.
是的。你是克里斯·奈特，对吗?
Yes. You are Chris Knight, aren't you?
我希望如此。我穿着他的内裤。
I hope so. I'm wearing his underwear.
这是一个笑话!我得到它!那是有趣的!
It's a joke! I get it! That's funny!
我就是忍不住。你们真有趣。
I just can't help it. You guys are such fun.
好吧，我们努力做到。对吗，迈克?
Well, we try to be. Isn't that right, Mike?
不。
No.
克里斯，雪莉会带你四处看看。
Chris, Sherry's gonna show you around the place.
你可以问她任何关于福利待遇、着装要求等问题。
You can ask her any questions about benefits, dress codes, whatever.
-待会在我办公室见好吧?——太棒了。
- I'll see you in my office later. Okay? - Great.
雪莉，好好照顾这个年轻人。
Sherry, take very good care of this young man.
他是全国十个最聪明的人之一!
He's one of the ten finest minds in the country!
我希望有一天我也能成为他们中的两个人。
Someday I hope to be two of them.
-你很漂亮。——谢谢。
- You are very beautiful. - Thank you.
我怎么样了?太闷了?
How'd I come off? Too stuffy?
你的行为举止显然不像美国十大头脑之一。
You certainly don't act like one of the top ten minds of America.
——真的吗?你见过几个?- 7。
- Really? How many have you met? - Seven.
——真的吗?——嗯。你会八。
- Really? - Mmm. You'll be eight.
麻省理工学院的霍斯特勒教授排名第六。
Professor Hostetler at MIT was number six.
老教授Hostetler吗?他不是死了吗?
Old Professor Hostetler? Isn't he dead?
他是现在。
He is now.
你好。我在找总统的新生茶?
Hello. I'm looking for the President's Freshman Tea?
哦,很好。
Oh, good.
我很高兴我们有一个。
I'm so glad we have one, then.
吉恩，太过分了。
Gene, it's too much.
-不，我不这么认为。——基因。
- No, I don't think so. - Gene.
-我是米奇·泰勒。——哦。海瑟薇教授的明星。
- This is Mitch Taylor. - Oh. Professor Hathaway's bright star.
-是的，先生-而且你已经在做他的项目了
- Yes, sir. - And you're already on his project.
-我们对你寄予厚望。-希望如此，先生。
- We expect great things from you. - Oh, I hope so, sir.
-哦，给点建议。-哦，谢谢
- Oh, a bit of advice. - Oh, uh, thank you.
总是……不。永远不要忘记检查你的推荐信。
Always... No. Never forget to check your references.
好的。谢谢你！
Okay. Thank you.
-我得走了哦。对不起。-没关系。
- Uh, I better be going. Oops. Sorry. - That's all right.
我觉得年轻人很喜欢我在口头上“趴下”，你说呢?
I think the young people enjoy it when I "get down" verbally, don't you?
嘿，葬礼在哪里举行?
Hey, where's the funeral?
万一你没注意到呢
♪ In case you hadn't noticed ♪
♬这是狗吃狗吃狗吃狗
♪ It's the dog eating dog Eating dog eating dog ♪
万一你没注意到呢
♪ In case you hadn't noticed ♪
你好吗，老兄?
How you doing, sport?
♬这是猫和老鼠……♪
♪ It's the cat and the mouse... ♪
嘿，鲍比，等一下，伙计!
Hey, Bobby, wait up, man!
看看他是不是在楼下房间里。他可能在里面。
Check if he's down in his room. He might be in there.
我们去骑自行车吧。
Let's go for a bike ride.
恰克，你哥哥打电话来了。
Chuck, your brother called.
-他从来不在家，伙计-不，我不知道他在哪
- He's never home, man. - No, I don't know where he is.
喂?
Hello?
-这是什么地方?-嗨。
- What kind of a place is this? - Hi.
如果重力逆转，你会做好准备吗?
Would you be prepared if gravity reversed itself?
我唯一不明白的是如何把零钱留在口袋里。
The only thing I can't figure out is how to keep the change in my pockets.
我懂了。裸体。
I've got it. Nudity.
我今早来过-你没收拾好，对吧?——没有。
I was here this morning-- - You didn't straighten up, did you? - No.
很好。我所有的脏东西都是按字母顺序排列的。
Good. All my filth is in alphabetical order.
例如，这个在“H”代表“玩具”下面。
This, for example, was under "H" for toy.
-那是什么?——这?这是阴茎担架。
- What is that? - This? It's a penis stretcher.
-你想试试吗?——不!
- You wanna try it? - No!
我在开玩笑。这是他一系列转移注意力的举动中的另一个，目的是试图逃避责任。——我…放下我的行李。现在我所有的包都空了。
I'm kidding. It's yet another in a long series of diversions - in an attempt to avoid responsibility. - I, uh... Dropped off my luggage. And now all my bags are empty.
你看，米奇，我以前是你。
You see, Mitch, I used to be you.
最近我很想我自己，所以我问海瑟薇能不能让我再和我一起住。
And, uh, lately I've been missing me, so I asked Hathaway if I could room with me again.
我把你的东西都放在最下面的抽屉里了。
So I put all your stuff away in the bottom drawer there.
运动夹克有问题，所以我把它扔了。鸭子!
Had trouble with the sports jacket, so I threw it out. Duck!
不错的反应。我是克里斯的骑士。
Nice reflexes. I'm Chris Knight.
-哦,不。-哦,是的。鸭子了!
- Oh, no. - Oh, yes. Duck again!
嘿!
Hey!
哦,我的上帝!
Oh, my God!
它朝油箱去了。鸭子!
It's heading for the gas tanks. Duck!
你认为这是一个发射问题还是一个设计问题?
Would you classify that as a launch problem or a design problem?
-我们落后太多了杰里-我们又不是在做奶酪三明治
- We're falling way behind, Jer. - We're not making cheese sandwiches.
——好的。下来!——嘿!
- All right. Get down! - Hey!
你在做什么?你疯了吗?你差点害死我们!
What are you doing? Are you crazy? You could have killed us!
那是院长之一，我不能和你在一起。
That is one of the deans, I cannot be seen with you.
我知道，杰里，但既然我在开车，你不觉得你应该躲起来吗?
I know, Jer, but since I'm driving, don't you think you should be hiding?
他看见我。
He saw me.
杰瑞，听着，我是来告诉你气候变了。
Jerry, look, I came here to tell you that the climate has changed.
我们需要在4个月内，而不是18个月内，找到一个可行的模型。
We need a working model within four months, not 18.
你不能支配创新，唐。
You can't dictate innovation, Don.
让我换一种说法。
Let me put it another way.
你知道我们在研发上花了多少钱吗?
You know all the money we've been spending on development?
是的。
Yes.
当一个项目被终止时，财务部门的人总会进行审计。
Well, when a project gets cut off, the finance boys always run an audit.
——我明白了。
- I see. - Mm.
小杰，你的老房子要装修一下了吧?
Having a little work done on the old place, huh, Jer?
欺诈是重罪。
Fraud is a felony.
你在看什么?你们是劳动者，你们应该劳动。
What are you looking at? You're laborers, you should be laboring.
这就是没受过教育的后果。
That's what you get for not having an education.
滚出去!继续，继续!滚出去!滚出去!
Get out of here! Go on, go on! Get out of here! Get out!
去长!
Go long!
——有!——是的!
- Got it! - Yeah!
——嘿!——是吗?
- Hey! - Yes?
-放下三明治走吧。——我吗?
- Put down the sandwiches and go. - Me?
不,尤达。是的,你!只是一点。
No, Yoda. Yeah, you! Just a bit.
-我没有-脑子?
- I don't have any-- - Brains?
——没有。三明治。-那你还有什么用?
- No. Sandwiches. - Then what good are you?
-我们应该吃什么?-你到底是不是那家餐厅的?
- What are we supposed to eat? - Are you from the restaurant or not?
不。我是米奇•泰勒。我是一名学生。
No. I'm Mitch Taylor. I'm a student.
海瑟薇医生让我上来。
Dr. Hathaway told me to come up here.
哦。
Oh.
你是新来的种马，是吗?
So, uh, you're the new stud, are you?
-什么意思?——螺柱。能人。大脑。
- How do you mean? - Stud. Hotshot. Brain.
-你才12岁，对吧?我15岁。你在等他吗，还是——?
- You're 12 years old, right? - I'm 15. Are you expecting him, or--?
是的。现在任何一分钟。您要点什么吗?
Yeah. Any minute now. Can I get you something?
——一个气球吗?-我应该看一下你的作品。
- A balloon? - I'm supposed to take a look at your work.
检查一下。
Check it over.
-检查一下?——好吧,是的。
- Check it over? - Well, yes.
——为了什么?-我想是错误吧。
- For what? - Mistakes, I guess.
-他说你们被困住了-不不不。
- He said you guys were stuck. - No, no, no.
让我们把事情弄清楚。
Let's get something very clear here.
杰瑞不在的时候，按我说的做。
Okay, when Jerry's not here, you do what I say.
从上帝到杰瑞再到我。明白了吗?
It goes from God to Jerry to me. Get it?
你好,杰瑞。
Hello, Jerry.
我告诉过你，肯特。你不能叫我的名字。
I told you before, Kent. You don't get to use my first name.
——我是吗?-你好吗，米奇?
- Did I? - How you doing, Mitch?
现在，我相信你们都会成为很快的朋友。
Now, I'm sure you'll all become fast friends.
-我们已经在路上了——好。
- We're well on our way already. - Good.
米奇被介绍完之后，我希望你能从他身上得到暗示。
After Mitch is brought up to date, I want you to take your cues from him.
他关于高效荧光化合物的想法是我见过的最新颖的。
His ideas on efficient fluorescent compounds are the most original I've seen.
所以从现在开始，米奇负责这个小组。
So from now on, Mitch is gonna be in charge of the group.
真的,杰瑞?
Really, Jerry?
-你又来了，肯特-是吗?
- You're doing it again, Kent. - Oh, am I?
-奈特在哪里?-他今天懒得来上班。
- Where is Knight? - He didn't bother to come in today.
嗯…——什么事 Bodie?-他说他不喜欢。
Uh... - Yes, Bodie? - He said he didn't feel like it.
我说:“最好是这样。”他说:“不然呢?”
I said, "You better." And he said, "Or what?"
我说"不然你就有麻烦了"他说:“堵住它!”
I said, "Or else you're gonna be in trouble." He said, "Jam it!"
这是一个精彩的故事。我注意到你不再口吃了。
That's a wonderful story. I noticed you stopped stuttering.
-一直在给自己做电击治疗。-提高电压。
- Been giving myself shock treatments. - Up the voltage.
-真遗憾他不在-那个小丑看看这个!
- I'm sorry he isn't here-- - That clown? Look at this!
我们听说他不来了。肯特决定不等他就开始。
We heard he wasn't coming. Kent decided to start without him.
荧光产量微不足道。我们认为样品被损坏了。
The fluorescent yield's insignificant. We think the sample's been damaged.
——什么?-显然是疏忽造成的。
- What? - Well, obviously the result of negligence.
准备另一份样品至少需要一周时间，我很担心。
It'll take us at least a week to prepare another sample, and I was afraid of this.
-你确定吗?——我们确定，非常确定
- Are you sure about that? - We're sure. Positive.
——对不起。打扰一下。-没有任何借口
- Excuse me. Excuse me. - There's simply no excuse for it.
-是啊，米奇，怎么了?-我想激光泵坏了。
- Yeah, Mitch, what is it? - I think the pump laser is down.
这看起来不对。看。
This doesn't look right. Look.
在那里。
There.
-嗯，现在好像好多了。——啊,史……该死，别碰别人的东西!
- Well, it seems to be all better now. - Aw, shi... Damn it, don't touch other people's things!
-肯特，我需要你——什么,杰里。
- Kent, I need you. - Anything, Jerry.
什么?你想让我帮你上二年级的课吗?
What? Do you want me to teach your sophomore class for you?
不，我需要你做一些复制，把目前所有的数据都复印一份。
No, I need you to do some duplicating, get copies made of all the data so far.
这样小米奇就可以开始了。他明天会检查所有东西。
So young Mitch can get started. He's gonna check everything tomorrow.
——我的荣幸。-然后去我的洗衣店。
- My pleasure. - Then after that, stop by my cleaners.
别想了。我喜欢它。
Don't give it a thought. I enjoy it.
-米奇，我们走吧?在这一时刻。——确定。
- Mitch, shall we? On the moment. - Sure.
我想这是上帝给杰瑞的，给你的，给洗衣店的。
Well, I guess it goes from God to Jerry, to you, to the cleaners.
肯特?
Right, Kent?
图书馆、图书馆……Two-oh-five。
Library, library... Two-oh-five.
欢迎来到太平洋科技的“冰上聪明人”节目。
Welcome to Pacific Tech's "Smart People on Ice."
让我们去滑冰。
Let's go skating.
-哎呀，冰做得太好了!-是啊，成功了，不是吗?
- Ick, the ice turned out so great! - Yeah, it worked, didn't it?
-你是怎么做到的?——哦,当然。
- How did you do it? - Oh, sure.
我告诉你，然后你告诉别人，接下来，我们就进入了另一个冰河世纪。
I tell you, then you tell somebody else, next thing you know, we're in the middle of another ice age.
-每个人都在滑冰!-就因为你偷懒，骑士!
- Everybody must be skating! - Just 'cause you're a slack, Knight!
-鼹鼠和巨魔。——什么?
- Moles and trolls. - What?
摩尔和巨魔。工作,工作,工作。我们永远见不到天日。
Moles and trolls. Work, work, work. We never see the light of day.
我们计划了好几个星期，他们只想学习。
We plan this thing for weeks and all they wanna do is study.
我厌恶。抱歉，但这不是我的风格。我沮丧。
I'm disgusted. I'm sorry, but it's not like me. I'm depressed.
我们没有人参加变异仓鼠比赛，只有一个人参加了居里夫人长相比赛，后来他被取消了资格。
We had no one at the mutant hamster races, one entry for the Madame Curie look-alike contest, and he was disqualified later.
我为什么要费心呢?
Why do I bother?
我们走吧!你们是什么，一群怪人吗?
Let's go! What are you, a bunch of weirdos?
-要樱桃吗?我自己种的。——樱桃?
- Want a cherry? I grow them myself. - A cherry?
好吧,推一次。
Okay, push once.
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
不,不是感情。不,我不是。我很失望。并不是很可怕。但仍然。
No, not emotionally. No, I'm not. I'm disappointed. Not terribly. But still.
它应该走得更远，更快。
It should have gone much further, much faster.
我知道问题出在哪里。显然是阻力系数。
I know what the problem is. It's obviously the drag coefficient.
我得重新设计一下刀片。我可以做到，没问题。
I'll just have to redesign the blades. I can do that, no problem.
但我必须把它们切掉，这需要工具和时间。
But I've got to cut them, and that takes tools and time.
-你知道这会持续多久吗?-再过半个小时吧。
- Do you know how long this will last? - Maybe another half an hour.
太好了。我可以做到，没问题。
That's great. I can do that, no problem.
——好的。你叫什么名字?——米奇。
- Okay. What's your name? - Mitch.
谢谢你的帮助，米奇。回头见。
Thank you for your help, Mitch. I'll see you later.
欢迎你!
You're welcome!
-那是谁?-我是乔丹我听说有新人了。你是吗?
- Who was that? - That-- I'm Jordan. I heard there was gonna be someone new. Are you it?
是的。
Yeah.
-你有床吗?-是的。
- Do you have a bed? - Yeah.
我想给你做一个，但你有一个。好吧，回头见。好吧,再见。
I'd make you one, but you have one. Okay, I'll see you later. Okay, bye.
再见。
Bye.
-这是怎么回事?——这?这是冰。
- What's all this supposed to be? - This? This is ice.
这就是水太冷时的情况。
This is what happens to water when it gets too cold.
这个吗?这是肯特。
This? This is Kent.
当人们在性方面太受挫时，就会发生这种事。
This is what happens to people when they get too sexually frustrated.
这应该能让你忙一阵子了。
This should keep you busy for a while.
加上你的常规课程负荷，一个月后你的大脑就会对木薯粉产生兴趣。
This plus your regular class load should turn your brains to tapioca in a month.
肯特，这太不公平了。我们要让你成为冬季嘉年华之王。
Kent, that is so unfair. And we were gonna make you king of the winter carnival.
是吗?
Yeah?
哦,哈哈哈。
Oh, ha-ha-ha.
我猜你也有份。你成功了吗?
I suppose you're in on this too. Did you make it?
-我没说。-那谁来清理呢?
- I'm not saying. - Well, who's gonna clean it up?
你不必这么做。它会直接从固态变成气态。
You don't have to. It's gonna go from solid form directly to gas.
哇。真的吗?它是什么?
Whoa. Really? What is it?
我不是说。但我可以告诉你，它相当罕见，非常不稳定。
I'm not saying. But I can tell you that it's fairly rare and very unstable.
就像你。
Just like you.
-你们是一群堕落的人。——我们是谁?
- You're a bunch of degenerates. - We are?
我发现你光着身子拿着那碗果冻。
I found you naked with that bowl of Jell-O.
-你没有。-这是真的。
- You did not. - This is true.
我又热又饿。好吗?
I was hot, and I was hungry. Okay?
不管怎样，我要告诉你，奈特。
And anyway, I got news for you, Knight.
-你已经不是这里的第一了。-第一什么?
- You're not number one here anymore. - Number one what?
这位强力鼠比你的排名高出20分。
Mighty Mouse over here beat your placement scores by over 20 points.
是的,你呢?你以为你很厉害吗?
Yeah, you did? You think you're hot stuff, huh?
不。
No.
是啊，也许你比我聪明。
Yeah, well, hey, maybe you are smarter than me.
但你能做到吗?
But can you do this?
哇!
Whoa!
伊克，冰块怎么了?
Ick, what's happening with the ice?
打开一扇窗!
Open a window!
呃——我融化!
Ick, I'm melting!
——它成功了!——这就是整洁!
- It worked! - That's neat!
-如果我们能阻止它爆炸的话。——爆炸?哦,上帝。
- Now if we can keep it from exploding. - Exploding? Oh, God.
嘿,我吐!你说爆炸是开玩笑吧?
Hey, Ick. You're just joking about exploding, right?
恶心吗?
Ick?
这是个玩笑，对吧?
It's a joke, right?
早上好。我看见你进来了。
Good morning. I saw you come in here.
我们昨晚见过，记得吗?我带着雪橇。我是乔丹。
We met last night, remember? I had the sled with me. I'm Jordan.
——在这里。我给你做了件毛衣。——昨晚?
- Here. I made you a sweater. - Last night?
这是我用手做的事。我希望我的尺寸是对的。
It's something I do with my hands. I hope I got the size right.
我有一个哥哥，我用他来比较身材。
I have a brother and I use him for size comparison.
我的眼力很好，所以我给你做了一个，因为我还没睡。
I have a pretty good eye, so I went ahead and made you one 'cause I was up.
-你在尿尿吗?-是的。
- Are you peeing? - Yeah.
哦。我从不睡觉。我不知道为什么。我把我的室友逼疯了。
Oh. I never sleep. I don't know why. I drove my roommate nuts.
他们只好用救护车把她送走。她现在没事了，但她得转院。
They had to take her away in ambulance. She's okay now, but she had to transfer.
我不知道这是不是我的错。
I don't know if that's my fault.
如果你想找人谈谈，告诉我。我就住在隔壁。
If you ever need to talk, let me know. I'm just a couple doors down.
我从不睡觉，好吗?
And I never sleep, okay?
——谢谢。我会的。-你说完了吗?
- Thanks. I will. - Are you done?
-呃，我没法开始。-因为我在这里?
- Uh, I can't start. - Because I'm here?
我想是的。
I think so.
——奇怪。我得走了。——我也是。
- Weird. Well, I have to go. - Me too.
再见。
Bye.
早上好!
Good morning!
——克里斯?——早上。
- Chris? - Morning.
你知道吗，今天早上我身上发生了奇怪的事。
You know, um, something strange happened to me this morning.
你是在做梦吗，梦见自己穿着长袍站在金字塔上，身边有1000个裸体女人尖叫着朝你扔咸菜?
Was it a dream where you see yourself standing in a robe on a pyramid with 1000 naked women screaming and throwing little pickles at you?
不。
No.
为什么只有我一个人有这个梦想?
Why am I the only person that has that dream?
那是液氮吗?
Is that liquid nitrogen?
嗯嗯。
Mm-hm.
——咖啡吗?——没有。
- Coffee? - No.
所以,发生了什么事?
So, what happened?
你知道有个人住在我们的衣橱里吗?
Did you know there's a guy living in our closet?
你也见过他?
You've seen him too?
他是谁?
Who is he?
Hollyfeld。
Hollyfeld.
-他为什么进我们的衣橱?-你为什么要进去?
- Why does he go in to our closet? - Why do you go in?
去拿我的衣服。但这不是他进去的原因。
To get my clothes. But that's not why he goes in there.
当然不是。他是你的两倍大。你的衣服根本不适合他。
Of course not. He's twice your size. Your clothes would never fit him.
是的。
Yeah.
问这些问题之前先想想，米奇。
Think before you ask these questions, Mitch.
比我高20分，觉得那样的大个子能穿他的衣服。
Twenty points higher than me, thinks a big guy like that can wear his clothes.
我从没想过会发生这种事
♪ I never thought this could happen ♪
我从没想过我会有这样的感觉
♪ I never thought I could feel this way ♪
直到今天这个奇怪的反应
♪ Till this strange reaction today ♪
你给了我新的感觉
♪ You give me a new sensation ♪
在一个没有名字的地方
♪ In a place that has no name ♪
总有东西告诉我，我再也不是原来的自己了
♪ Something tells me I'll never be the same ♪
现在一切都变了
♪ Now it's all changed ♪
♬我在坠落，坠落
♪ I'm fallin', fallin' ♪
♬♪，♬♪
♪ Fallin', fallin' ♪
♬我在坠落，坠落
♪ I'm fallin', fallin' ♪
♪我开始滑落♪
♪ I began to slip ♪
我不知道接下来会发生什么
♪ I didn't know what was coming next ♪
即使这样我也没有准备好
♪ Even so I was not prepared for this ♪
♪还没准备好
♪ Not prepared for this ♪
我曾经以为什么都不重要
♪ I used to think nothing mattered ♪
现在我看到了可能性
♪ Now I see possibilities ♪
你给我指明了新的方向
♪ You showed a new direction ♪
♪对我♪
♪ To me ♪
这一切都变了
♪ And it's all changed ♪
♬我在坠落，坠落
♪ I'm fallin', fallin' ♪
♬♪，♬♪
♪ Fallin', fallin' ♪
♬我在坠落，坠落
♪ I'm fallin', fallin' ♪
♬♪，♬♪
♪ Fallin', fallin' ♪
♪我开始滑落♪
♪ I began to slip ♪
我不知道接下来会发生什么
♪ I didn't know what was coming next ♪
即使这样我也没有准备好
♪ Even so I was not prepared for this ♪
♪还没准备好
♪ Not prepared for this ♪
♬我在坠落，坠落
♪ I'm fallin', fallin' ♪
♬♪，♬♪
♪ Fallin', fallin' ♪
福林♪♪”
♪ Fallin' ♪
.．.加上Y = 0。
...plus Y equals zero.
“就是这样。”
"This is it."
快，快离开这里!滚出去!继续,得到!
Come on, get out of here! Get out of here! Go on, get!
-你找我?——奈特。
- You wanted to see me? - Mr. Knight.
准时。这在现在有点不寻常。
Right on time. That's a little unusual these days.
-你还跑步吗?-只有在被追逐的时候。
- You still run? - Only when chased.
-那是什么味道?-一定是那只狗。
- What's that smell? - Must be the dog.
——这是爆米花。-是的，先生，我知道
- That's popcorn. - Yes, sir. I know.
把它拿开。我受不了爆米花。我讨厌爆米花。
Get it away from me. I can't stand popcorn. I hate popcorn.
来吧，把它放在那边。
Come on, put it over there.
很好。现在我知道送你什么生日礼物了。
Good. Now I know what to get you for your birthday.
我想我们的地位上升了，是吧，杰瑞?
I guess we're moving up in the world, eh, Jerry?
-它很优雅。——谢谢。尽量不要碰任何东西。
- It's very elegant. - Thank you. Try not to touch anything.
-可以吗，先生?-这是橡木的，又不是胶合板。
- Is this okay, sir? - It's oak, not plywood for God's sake.
-和以前的地方相比变化很大。——鞋子。
- Quite a change from the old place. - Shoes.
听着，我想在实验室里多见到你。
Look, I want to start seeing a lot more of you in the lab.
好吧。我要增加体重。
Fine. I'll gain weight.
-你真是个有趣的孩子，克里斯。-谢谢，杰瑞，我们尽力了。
- You're a very funny boy, Chris. - Thanks, Jerry, we try.
你可以坐。
You can sit.
当我第一次带你来这所学校时，我以为你会成为另一个爱因斯坦。
When I first brought you into this school, I thought you'd become another Einstein.
-你在你的路上。然后呢?-我去理发了。
- You were well on your way. And then? - I got a haircut.
-你让我失望了，克里斯。-你也是我，杰瑞。
- You're disappointing me, Chris. - And you me, Jerry.
-是关于我们的交易-我知道，杰瑞。和…我推动你的项目比学校里任何三个学生都要多。
- Look, it's about our deal. - I know, Jerry. And... I have advanced your project more than any three students on campus.
那是昨天吃的。你今天为我做了什么?
That was yesterday. What have you done for me today?
嗯…
Well...
5月中旬我要5兆瓦。
I want five megawatts by mid-May.
杰瑞，我觉得你可能对这一切有点着迷了。
Uh, Jerry, I think you might be getting a little obsessive about all this.
我收留了米奇，好吗?
Now, I took in Mitch, okay?
他进展得很好。他在为你竭尽全力。
He's coming along fine. He's working his guts out for you.
-那你到底想要什么?- 5月中旬我要5兆瓦。
- So, what exactly do you want? - I want five megawatts by mid-May.
听着，我不在乎你是否傲慢。
Look, I don't care if you're arrogant.
我不在乎你是否无礼。
I don't care if you're disrespectful.
但你的态度让米奇分心了。而我不会这样做。
But your attitude's distracting Mitch. And that I won't have.
规则已经改变了。我想在五月中旬之前拿到。
The rules have changed. I want it by mid-May.
杰瑞，我觉得你忘了一个小细节。
Jerry, I think that you're just forgetting about one little detail.
那我就走了。我走了，我已成历史。我是鬼马小精灵。
And that's I'm out of here. I'm gone, I'm history. I'm Casper.
我毕业。
I'm graduating.
要想毕业，你需要上我的课，亲爱的孩子。
To graduate, you need my course, dear boy.
看来我对你做什么，去哪里有发言权了。
So it seems that I have a say about what you do and where you go.
所以从现在开始，你和米奇醒着的时候都要待在实验室里。
So from now on, you and Mitch will spend every waking moment in the lab.
你要在我的期限前解决我的电力问题。
And you will solve my power problem and solve it by my deadline.
杰里……如果你以为威胁我就能让我做你的奴隶……这一点你是对的。
Jerry... If you think that by threatening me you can get me to be your slave... that's where you're right.
但是我这么说只是因为我在乎。
But-- And I'm only saying this because I care.
——有很多不含咖啡因的品牌和真正的咖啡一样美味。
--there are a lot of decaffeinated brands that are just as tasty as the real thing.
我没开玩笑，克里斯。
I'm not kidding, Chris.
我也不是，杰瑞。
Neither am I, Jerry.
嗨,米奇。
Hey, Mitch.
帮我个忙，好吗?
Do me a favor, will you?
这味道。拜托，你不会伤害我的感情的。
Taste this. Come on, you won't hurt my feelings.
尝一下就行了，好了。
Just give it a taste-- Yeah, there you go.
什么,太甜?
What, too sweet?
-什么事?-我不知道，在实验室里
- What is it? - I don't know, it was in the lab.
哦!
Oh!
别紧张，只是酸奶而已。嗯。
Relax, it's just yogurt. Mmm.
-米奇，米奇，你没事吧?-不，我没有。
- Mitch, Mitch, are you all right? - No, I'm not.
这种电和化学氰化物的结合是愚蠢的。
This combination of electrical plus chemical cyanide is dumb.
我们走错方向了。
We're going in the wrong direction.
你是唯一知道怎么用这垃圾的人。
You're the only one that knows how to use this garbage.
你不会在这里。最后，我觉得我的大脑被炸了。
You're never here. And, finally, I think I'm getting brain-fried.
好吧，米奇，我会补偿你的。
Okay, Mitch, I'm gonna make it up to you.
我们暂停一下，把它放下。
Let's just pause, put that down.
让我们先退一步。
Let's just take a step back.
不，我错了，对不起，往前走一步。
No, I was wrong, sorry, take a step forward.
现在退一步。
Now take a step back.
和进步。然后退后一步。然后我们跳恰恰舞。
And step forward. Then step back. And then we're cha-cha-ing.
-你能别说了吗?我是认真的!-好吧，我也是认真的
- Will you stop it? I'm serious! - Okay, I'm serious too.
让我们给这个宝贝充电吧。把你知道的都给我。来吧。
Let's charge this baby up. Give me everything you got. Come on.
我得去笼子里连接电容器。
I gotta go in the cage to connect the capacitors.
好了，现在是工作时间。
Okay, this is work time.
-你还好吗，米奇?——好。别催我。
- How you doing there, Mitch? - Fine. Don't rush me.
好吧，慢慢来。一切都很好。
Okay, just take your time. Everything's fine.
怎么花了这么长时间?
What is taking so long?
我来了。
I'm coming.
充电。
Charging.
色调。
Shades.
-你在干什么?——等待。
- What are you doing? - Waiting.
-哦,不。——放松。
- Oh, no. - Relax.
那只是变电站的保险丝。马上就会开了。
That's just the fuses at the substation. It'll be back on in a minute.
也许我不该在大楼的变压器上短路。
Maybe I shouldn't have shorted across the building transformer.
但更重要的是，我们被指控了吗?
But, more importantly, did we get a charge?
你会做什么呢?
What'd you do?
-等一下!-来吧，斯普特尼克。
- Wait a minute! - Come on, Sputnik.
你说你需要帮助，那就开始吧。
You said you wanted help, so here we go.
——什么?——美丽的心灵。
- What? - Beautiful minds.
克里斯，我们还有工作。
Chris, we have work.
我们要去工作了。艰苦的工作。
We're going to work. Hard work.
-你一定花了好几个小时——什么?-我们去看看吧。
- This must've taken you hours. What--? - Well, let's go find out.
我说过他们会重开的。
I told you they'd turn it back on.
——这是什么?-那是激光束，笨蛋
- What's this? - It's a laser beam, bozo.
-这是干什么用的?——不是。在哪里。
- What's it for? - Not what. Where.
——什么?哦!——遵循它。这是一个惊喜。
- What? Oh! - Follow it. It's a surprise.
你喜欢它吗?
You like it?
嘿，分束器是干什么用的?
Hey, what's the beam splitter for?
-你们是怎么回事?-需要把一切都说清楚吗?
- What's the matter with you guys? - Need everything spelled out for you?
来吧，让我们晒日光浴!
Come on, let's tan!
我们有一个给米奇的。
We have one for Mitch.
♬并把他们放在钢笔♬
♪ And puttin' them in a pen ♪
♬她想做的只是跳舞，跳舞
♪ And all she wants to do is Dance, dance ♪
♬叛军一直是叛军，我不知道从什么时候开始
♪ Rebels been rebels Since I don't know when ♪
进来吧，南太平洋在召唤你。
Come on in, the South Pacific calls you.
-克里斯，那些女孩是谁?-我知道他们不是本地人。
- Chris, who are the girls? - They're not from around here, I'd know.
-他们来自附近的一所大学。——哪一个?
- They're from a nearby college. - Which one?
旺达·特罗斯勒美容学校。
The Wanda Trossler School of Beauty.
——他们美容师吗?——没有。
- They're beauticians? - Not yet.
-我不知道。-你的天赋可能会打动他们。
- I don't know. - Your genius might impress them.
-我不知道怎么做。——好吧,好吧。
- I don't see how. - Okay, okay.
考虑到你是什么样的人，你所处的环境，你必须承认这很有可能是你一生中唯一一次做爱的机会。
Given the type of people you are and the environment you're in, you have to admit the strong probability that this may be the only chance you will ever have in your entire lives to have sex.
想想。
Think about it.
是啊!
Yeah!
♬她想要派对，她想要堕落
♪ She wants to party She wants to get down ♪
♬她想做的就是她想做的就是跳舞
♪ All she wants to do is All she wants to do is dance ♪
的命运!我现在抓住她了。
Destiny! I've got her now.
♪政府在男厕所装了窃听器♪在当地的迪斯科舞厅♪
♪ Government bugged the men's room ♪ In the local disco lounge ♪
-别吃那个。——嗯?
- Don't eat that. - Huh?
你难道不知道吃那种东西会让你的胸部变大吗?
Don't you know that eating that stuff can give you very large breasts?
哦,我的上帝。我太迟了。
Oh, my God. I'm too late.
而她想做的只是跳舞
♪ And all she wants to do is dance ♪
那也不能阻止男孩们赚一两个钱
♪ That don't keep the boys From makin' a buck or two ♪
♬她想做的只是跳舞，跳舞
♪ And all she wants to do is Dance, dance ♪
唐，别表现得好像我不想让自己的发明成功似的。
Don, don't act as if I don't want my own invention to work.
-一天就那么几个小时。-可以走了，海瑟薇医生
- There are only so many hours in the day. - Ready to go, Dr. Hathaway.
逼我没用，唐你得告诉他们。
Pushing me doesn't help, Don. You'll have to tell them that.
好的。拿出点成果来，不然他们就会找别人。
Okay. Start showing some results, or they'll find somebody else.
——卷胶带。——哦,真的吗?谁?
- Roll tape. - Oh, really? Who?
那你的大玩具就没了。
Then you won't have your big toys anymore.
我是最棒的，唐。你以为你在和谁打交道?
I am the best, Don. Who do you think you're dealing with?
你怎么敢这么做。我得继续。
How dare you try this. I have to go on.
我觉得这段对话太没品味了。我真的。
I think this whole conversation is in incredibly poor taste. I really do.
-王八蛋——混蛋。
- Son of a bitch. - Asshole.
欢迎做客主持人杰罗姆·海瑟薇博士的节目。
Welcome to Everything, with your host, Dr. Jerome Hathaway.
由达灵顿电子仪器公司资助。
Funded by a grant from Darlington Electronic Instruments.
现在有请海瑟薇博士。
And now Dr. Hathaway.
嗨，我是《万物》的杰瑞·海瑟薇。
Hi, I'm Jerry Hathaway, with Everything.
今晚，我们将讨论一些我们大多数人认为理所当然的事情。
Tonight, we are going to look at something that most of us take for granted.
结肠。
The colon.
它看起来像什么?
What does it look like?
嘿，快出来。
Hey, get out of there.
肯特!
Kent!
——切!——什么?
- Cut! - What?
-你站在提词器前。-噢。嗯，我不知道。
- You're in front of the teleprompter. - Ow. Well, I didn't know.
-我有事要告诉你。-你帮我拿干洗的衣服了吗?
- There's something I have to tell you. - Did you get my dry cleaning?
是的，但有件事你应该知道。
Yes, but there's something you should know.
-肉汁渍。-不，不，是说出来的
- The gravy stain. - No, no, that came out.
克里斯和米奇，他们没在工作，他们在派对上。
Chris and Mitch, they're not working, they're at a party.
与女孩。
With girls.
-我要你带我去。——我的荣幸。
- I want you to show me where. - My pleasure.
但我从没想过我会触碰到你
♪ But I never thought That I'd be touching you ♪
♪我怎么会知道♪
♪ How was I to know ♪
♪我会让自己的感情走远
♪ I'd let my feelings go ♪
在黑夜过去之前，我将属于你
♪ And that I'd be yours Before the night was through ♪
是的♪♪
♪ Yeah ♪
♬一夜风流
♪ One night love affair ♪
♪试着让我们不在乎♪
♪ Tryin' to make like we don't care ♪
-嗨，你忙吗?——是的。不。不。
- Hi, are you busy? - Yes. No. No.
你愿意帮我测试呼吸器吗?来吧!
Do you wanna help test my rebreather? Come on!
当然!
Sure!
♪假装它不存在♪
♪ Pretendin' it ain't there ♪
这其实是一个简单的原理。它基本上是一个过滤器。
It's actually a simple principle. It's basically a filter.
它把二氧化碳释放出来，把氧气放回去，就像植物一样。但没有泡沫。
It lets the CO2 out and the O2 back in, like a plant. But no bubbles.
-你怎么不…?——变细?我不是同性恋!
- How come you're not, uh--? - Necking? I'm not gay!
不,聚会。
No, partying.
哦。因为我才19岁，聪明又好动。
Oh. Because I'm 19 and I'm brilliant and I'm hyperkinetic.
所以男人们有点害怕。
So guys are a little afraid.
也许，如果我停下来想一想，我就会心烦意乱。
Probably, if I stopped to think about it, I'd be upset.
我觉得你人很好。
I think you're very nice.
但是我失去了控制
♪ But I lose control ♪
我也觉得你很好。
I think you're nice too.
你想尝尝这个吗?
Do you want to try this?
是的。
Yeah.
-水里比较轻。-你呢?
- It's lighter in the water. - How about you?
我们都在追寻着什么
♪ We were both reachin' out For somethin' ♪
♪对，对——♪
♪ Yeah, yeah-- ♪
嘿，音乐是怎么回事?
Hey, what's with the music?
泰勒!
Taylor!
来吧!把它打开!
Come on! Turn it back on!
你应该在实验室里的。
You're supposed to be in the lab.
我只是你来太平洋理工是工作的，不是当医生的。
I was, I just-- You're at Pacific Tech to work, not to play doctor.
-我在工作。我刚被耽搁了。-是啊，奈特呢?
- I was working. I just got delayed. - Yeah, where's Knight?
-你们两个都让我恶心。什么?是的。哦。-肯特!
- You both make me sick. What? Yeah. Oh. - Kent!
我冒了很大的风险推荐了一个15岁的女孩。
I took a big chance in recommending a 15-year-old.
我现在知道我犯了个错误。希望你为自己感到骄傲。
I can see now that I made a mistake. Hope you're proud of yourself.
-海瑟薇博士?——什么?
- Dr. Hathaway? - What?
你化了妆吗?
Are you wearing makeup?
什么?
What?
♬一夜风流
♪ One night love affair ♪
炮弹!
Cannonball!
我还需要一门课程来完成我的人文学科学分。
I need just one more course to complete my humanities credits.
不，我不知道该怎么跟你说。
No, I don't know what to tell you, man.
是的，我想给比尔·泰勒太太打对方付费电话。
Yes, I'd like to make a collect call to Mrs. Bill Taylor.
——啊。快点，快点，快点。——米奇•泰勒。
- Ah. Come on, come on, come on. - Mitch Taylor.
-我有个主意。我有个好主意。——什么?
- I got an idea. I got a great idea. - What?
——什么?-按住!
- What? - Hold it down!
妈妈,我……
Mom, I...
我想回家。
I want to come home.
-妈妈，你在听吗?-宝贝，你听起来很沮丧。
- Mom, are you there? - Baby, you sound upset.
——怎么了?-我不喜欢这里了。
- What's wrong? - I don't like it here anymore.
我想回家和你住在一起。
I wanna come home and live with you.
你把我的房间租出去了?妈妈,谁?
You rented out my room?! Mom, to who?
你还记得埃切瓦里亚先生吗，他是水管工。
You remember Mr. Echevarria, he's the plumber.
——倾听。-妈妈
- Listen. - Mom--
你昨晚在哪里?
So where were you last night?
实验室，你应该在的地方。
The lab, where you were supposed to be.
嗯。是的。
Mmm. Yeah.
乔丹说海瑟薇对你下手了。他到底做了什么?
Jordan said that Hathaway got down on you. What exactly did he, uh--?
让我先考虑一下，然后再打给你。
Let me hold on to that thought and get back to you.
——妈妈。-妈妈，你在听吗?
- Mom. - Mom, are you there?
宝贝，你听起来很沮丧。怎么了?
Baby, you sound upset. What's wrong?
-我不喜欢这里了。-我想回家和你一起住。
- I don't like it here anymore. - I wanna come home and live with you.
不是让你喜欢，而是让你去做。
It's not for you to like, it's for you to do.
你现在15岁了。
You're 15 years old now.
我想回家和你住在一起。
I wanna come home and live with you.
-你想和我还有爸爸一起住吗?-是的。和爸爸。
- You want to live with me and Daddy? - Yeah. And Dad too.
-我想回到高中。-爸爸把你的房间租出去了
- I wanna go back to high school. - Daddy's rented out your room.
我的房间吗?
My room?
-妈，给谁?!-埃切瓦里亚先生，他是水管工
- Mom, to who?! - Mr. Echevarria, he's the plumber.
-埃切瓦里亚先生和我一起住。-妈，我不想再呆在这里了。
- Mr. Echevarria and I can share it. - Mom, I don't wanna stay here anymore.
米琪，这听起来可不像妈妈的小兵。
Now, Mitchie, that doesn't sound like Mama's little soldier.
米奇，是你爸爸。
Mitch, it's your dad.
——嗨,爸爸。-你在哭吗?
- Hi, Dad. - Are you crying?
-是的，先生，很抱歉-我希望没人看见你。
- Yes, sir. I'm sorry. - Well, I hope nobody sees you.
-我只是个孩子。-你从来不只是个孩子。
- I'm just a kid. - You've never been just a kid.
好的。
Okay.
如果你想走，就走吧。
If you wanna leave, go ahead.
但是，你会错过乐趣的。
But, uh, you're gonna miss the fun.
什么乐趣?
What fun?
伊克发明了一种新病毒我们要在肯特的房间里释放它
Ick invented a new virus and we're going to release it in Kent's room.
那天晚上我需要你的帮助而你只想去派对。
The other night I needed your help and you just wanted to party.
我确实帮过你。我试着帮你放松。
I did help you. I tried to help you relax.
被美容师冷落不是我的放松方式。
Being snubbed by beauticians is not my idea of relaxing.
学生美容师。
Student beauticians.
我以为这地方不一样。但这是一样的。
You know, I thought this place was different. But it's just the same.
高中时，他们把我塞进邮箱。我告诉过你吗?
In high school, they stuffed me in a mailbox. Did I tell you that?
我的老师不喜欢我，因为我比他们聪明。
My teachers disliked me because I was smarter than they were.
学生们讨厌我，因为我搞砸了钟形曲线。听起来是不是很熟悉?
Students hated me because I blew the bell curve. Does that sound familiar?
米奇，我和你一样。
Mitch, I was just like you.
我妈妈过去常给我穿上白衬衫和油炸小甜甜圈，保证不会有女孩和我说话。
My mother used to dress me in white shirts and Hush Puppies, guaranteeing that a girl would never talk to me.
当我第一次来这里的时候，有三年时间我一直在学习。
When I first came here, for three years I studied all the time.
——你呢?-是的。
- You? - Yeah.
然后有一天晚上，当我坐在这把椅子上时，我看到了一个幻象。
Then one night, when sitting in this chair right here, I had a vision.
——什么?——Hollyfeld。
- What? - Hollyfeld.
-壁橱里的那个人?——Lazlo Hollyfeld。
- The guy in the closet? - Lazlo Hollyfeld.
我跟着他进了壁橱，进了蒸汽通道。
And I followed him into the closet, down into the steam tunnels.
在那里我看到了我这辈子见过的最恶心的事。
And there I saw the most disgusting thing I've ever seen in my life.
——什么?-穿着睡衣的霍利菲尔德
- What? - Hollyfeld in his pajamas.
——所以呢?-所以我跟他谈了
- So? - So I talked to him.
——你做了吗?-是的。
- You did? - Yeah.
他在70年代是这里的头号种马。
He used to be the number one stud around here in the '70s.
比你我加起来还聪明。
Smarter than you and me put together.
-发生什么事了?他破解了吗?——是的。
- So, what happened? Did he crack? - Yes.
他严重开裂。
He cracked, severely.
——为什么?-他热爱他的工作。
- Why? - He loved his work.
-那有什么不对吗?——什么都没有。但这就是他所做的一切。
- Well, what's wrong with that? - Nothing. But that's all he did.
他喜欢解决问题，喜欢想出答案。
He loved solving problems, he loved coming up with the answers.
但他认为答案就是一切的答案。
But he thought that the answers were the answers for everything.
只有科学，没有哲学。
All science, no philosophy.
有一天，有人告诉他他做的东西正在杀人。
One day, someone tells him that the stuff he was making was killing people.
那么，你想说什么?我会死在蒸汽隧道里吗?
So, what's your point? I'm gonna end up in a steam tunnel?
-是的。——什么?
- Yeah. - What?
如果你再这样下去，你就是。
You are, if you keep up like this.
米奇，你不需要离开这里。
Mitch, you don't need to run away from here.
当你聪明的时候，人们需要你。
When you're smart, people need you.
-你可以创造性地运用你的思维。-是的。
- You can use your mind creatively. - Yeah.
-我注意到你学习不太努力。宾果。
- I noticed you don't study too hard. - Bingo.
是啊，但如果我留下，我该怎么办?
Yeah, but if I stay, what should I do?
首先，报复肯特。这是一种道德义务。
First thing, get even with Kent. It's a moral imperative.
-是的。——是的!
- Yeah. - Yeah!
-现在你试试。——是的!
- Now you try it. - Yeah!
——这很好。现在让我们解压。——正确的。
- That's good. Now let's unpack. - Right.
所以达灵顿才这么可爱。你会得到一切。
Which is what makes Darlington so sweet. You get everything.
-是的，但奈特已经锁定了。-也许他有，也许他没有。
- Yeah, but Knight's got that locked. - Maybe he does, maybe he doesn't.
好吧!嘘!
Okay! Psst!
来吧。来吧，伙计们。他走了。
Come on. Come on, you guys. He's gone.
肯特把他的名字放在盘子上。
Kent put his name on his plate.
我妈对我的内裤也是这么处理的。
My mom does the same thing with my underwear.
你妈在你内裤里放车牌?你怎么坐?
Your mother puts license plates in your underwear? How do you sit?
嗨,肯特。
Hey, Kent.
这是你的车。
That's your car.
肯特，你知道你不应该把车停在校园里。
Kent, you know you're not supposed to park that on campus.
你知道，这一点都不好笑。
You know, this isn't funny.
-你这次太过分了。-我有帮手。
- You've gone too far this time. - I had help.
你,嗯?
You, huh?
我会抓到你们的。
I'm gonna get you guys.
海瑟薇医生会知道的。你会后悔的!
Dr. Hathaway's gonna hear all about this. You'll rue the day!
- "后悔"?谁会这样说话?-我不知道。
- "Rue the day"? Who talks like that? - I don't know.
哇。你好。
Wow. Hello.
嗨。
Hi.
嗯…
Well...
听着，杰瑞让我过来。他让你做什么了?
Listen, Jerry asked me to drop by. What did he ask you to do?
——什么?-你听不懂哪个词?
- What? - Which word didn't you understand?
-你是来开会的吗?什么会议?
- Are you here for the meeting? - What meeting?
-我不知道。——好的。
- I don't know. - Okay.
-听着，我只是在等——太棒了。
- Look, I'm just waiting. - Great.
归根结底，如果你做不到，我们就得找别人。
What it comes down to, if you can't do it, we'll have to get somebody else.
-我有时间表，医生。-我们很亲密，一切都会好的。
- I have a timetable, doctor. - We're very close, everything'll be fine.
唐，记住，你为我工作。我想我已经明白我的意思了，不是吗?
Don, remember, you work for me. I think I've made my point, haven't I?
——晶莹剔透。真的。-有什么要告诉我的吗，孩子们?
- Crystal clear. Really. - Anything I should know about, boys?
-我马上就来。——再见,杰里。,祝你好运。
- I'll be with you in a moment. - Goodbye, Jerry. And good luck.
苏珊。
Susan.
我想我们该说再见了。
Well, I guess this is goodbye.
我很抱歉我根本没机会了解你。
I'm sorry I didn't get a chance to know you at all.
我受不了了。你这辈子见过这样的尸体吗?
I can't stand it. Have you ever seen a body like this before in your life?
-她正好是我女儿。——哦。好吧，那我猜你有。
- She happens to be my daughter. - Oh. Well, then I guess you have.
——来,唐?-是的。
- Coming, Don? - Yeah.
说真的，听着，如果有什么我能为你做的或者…更重要的是，你告诉我，好吗?
Seriously, listen, if there's ever anything I can do for you or... more the point, to you, you let me know, okay?
你能用鸡鸡在木板上钉钉子吗?
Can you hammer a spike through a board with your penis?
-现在不行。-女孩应该有自己的标准。
- Not right now. - A girl's gotta have her standards.
苏珊。
Susan.
-那是一个非常聪明的女孩。-你知道你在干什么吗?
- That is a very smart girl. - What do you think you're doing?
-你说过过来。-离地毯远点。
- You said, come over. - Stay off the rug.
脱掉你的鞋子。
Take off your shoes.
-怎么了，医生?——坐下来。
- What's up, doc? - Sit down.
-那些人是谁?-你对我已经没用了!
- Who were those guys? - You are no longer of any use to me!
用这种有趣的方式开始对话。
Interesting way to open up a conversation.
我要把达灵顿的工作给肯特。
I'm giving Kent the Darlington job.
你突然发现幽默了吗?你给了我这份工作。
Did you suddenly find humor? You gave me the job.
-你需要一个学位。-我能通过你的考试。
- You need a degree. - I can pass your exam.
就算过了，也不会过。
Even if you pass, you don't pass.
-你为什么不现在就走?——好,好。我去找梅雷迪思医生。
- Why don't you leave right now? - Okay, fine. I'll go to Dr. Meredith.
光我在激光方面所做的工作就应该获得学位。
The work I've done on laser alone should merit a degree.
你想跟他说什么都可以。他会相信谁，你还是我?
You can tell him anything you like. Who will he believe, you or me?
-你不能这么做——完成。你出去了。现在出去!
- You can't do this. - It's done. You're out. Now get out!
我保证你再也不会干这行了。
And I'll make sure you never work in this field again.
-你这个难以置信的混蛋-放心吧。
- You unbelievable bastard. - Count on it.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
自我实现。我想起苏格拉底的不朽名言，他说:
Self-realization. I was thinking of the immortal words of Socrates, who said:
“我喝了什么?”
"I drank what?"
有什么问题吗?
Is there something wrong?
海瑟薇要让我退学了。
Hathaway is going to flunk me out of school.
——为什么?-我搞砸了。
- Why? - I screwed up.
-你打算怎么办?-我想我该走了。
- What are you gonna do? - I guess I'll leave.
你不能这么做。你会失败的!
You can't do that. You'll be a failure!
谢谢你,米奇。
Thank you, Mitch.
你就是不能走。你欠我10块钱。
You just can't leave. You owe me 10 bucks.
你现在不能辞职。
You can't quit now.
如果没有别的原因，只是为了看一场5兆瓦的激光大火。只有一次。
If for no other reason than just to see a five-megawatt laser fire. Just once.
那太好了。
That would be nice.
-你得有始有终。-谁说的?
- You gotta finish what you start. - Who said that?
你知道的。
You know that.
没错,米奇。但这并不能激励别人。
That's right, Mitch. But that is no way to motivate somebody.
你得报复杰瑞·海瑟薇。
You've got to get even with Jerry Hathaway.
这是一种道德义务。
It's a moral imperative.
说得好。
That's a good point.
♬第一，是一段艰难的时光
♪ Number one is a hard time In the making ♪
♪二号是我不会乘坐的飞机♪
♪ Number two is the one plane I'm not taking ♪
♪三号单膝跪地只为一个象征♪
♪ Number three goes on one knee For a token ♪
♪4号是救命稻草但是它坏了♪
♪ Number four is the short straw But it's broken ♪
♪我愿意付出我的一切只为成为第一
♪ I'd give my all just to be number one ♪
♬第一，是一段艰难的时光
♪ Number one is a hard time In the making ♪
-♬不给♬-♬不给♬
- ♪ Don't give ♪ - ♪ Don't give ♪
-那该死的那该死的那该死的那
- ♪ A damn ♪ - ♪ A damn ♪
-♬还有什么♬-♬还有什么♬
- ♪ What else ♪ - ♪ What else ♪
-♪我是♪♪我是♪
- ♪ I am ♪ - ♪ I am ♪
冥冥中的人冥冥中的人
♪ The man in the making ♪
♪，♪，♪
♪ Making, making, making ♪
♬五号是一个糟糕的乘坐，绕着赛道♬
♪ Number five is a bad ride 'Round the circuit ♪
♬第六是一个悲伤的梦当你工作♬
♪ Number six is a sad dream When you're working ♪
如果我能成为第一，我愿意付出全世界
♪ I'd give the world If I could be number one ♪
♬第一条是唯一的救赎之路
♪ Number one is the one way To salvation ♪
-♬我愿意♬-♬我愿意♬
- ♪ I'll do ♪ - ♪ I'll do ♪
-♪我最好的♪♪我最好的♪
- ♪ My best ♪ - ♪ My best ♪
-♪打败♪♪打败♪
- ♪ To beat ♪ - ♪ To beat ♪
-♬剩下的♬-♬剩下的♬
- ♪ The rest ♪ - ♪ The rest ♪
-冥冥中冥冥中冥冥中冥冥中冥冥中冥冥中冥冥中
- ♪ And be ♪ - ♪ And be ♪
♪全国最好的♪
♪ The best in the nation ♪
♬国家，国家，国家
♪ Nation, nation, nation ♪
-♬我赌♬-♬我赌♬
- ♪ I'll stake ♪ - ♪ I'll stake ♪
-我的主张♬-♬我的主张♬
- ♪ My claim ♪ - ♪ My claim ♪
-♬我将让♬-♬我将让♬
- ♪ I'll make ♪ - ♪ I'll make ♪
♪我的名字♪♪我的名字♪
- ♪ My name ♪ - ♪ My name ♪
-♪我的爱♪♪我的爱♪
- ♪ My love ♪ - ♪ My love ♪
♬我的游戏，我的职业
♪ My game, my vocation ♪
♪天意，天意，天意
♪ Vocation, vocation, vocation ♪
♪我愿意付出我的一切只为成为第一
♪ I'd give my all just to be number one ♪
♪我愿意付出我的一切，只为了成为♪
♪ I'd give my all just to be number ♪
♪我愿意付出我的一切只为成为第一
♪ I'd give my all just to be number one ♪
-♬不给♬-♬不给♬
- ♪ Don't give ♪ - ♪ Don't give ♪
-那该死的那该死的那该死的那
- ♪ A damn ♪ - ♪ A damn ♪
-♬还有什么♬-♬还有什么♬
- ♪ What else ♪ - ♪ What else ♪
-♪我是♪♪我是♪
- ♪ I am ♪ - ♪ I am ♪
冥冥中的人冥冥中的人
♪ The man in the making ♪
不。维托,又不是。
No. Vito, not again.
别放在邮箱里，维多。
Not in the mailbox, Vito.
——不!——米奇。
- No! - Mitch.
米奇。
Mitch.
你为什么不去睡一会儿呢?
Why don't you get some sleep.
我们又不是在开车什么的。我希望你还在成长。
It's not like we're driving or anything. You're still a growing boy, I hope.
嘿,Lazlo。
Hey, Lazlo.
Lazlo吗?
Lazlo?
哦。
Oh.
那就是我。你好。
That's me. Hello.
我一直在观察你。
I've been watching you.
谢谢。
Thanks.
我觉得你考试可能需要帮助，所以我找到了海瑟薇在每次期末考试中问过的所有问题。
Well, I thought you might need some help with the test, so I found every question Hathaway's ever asked on every final he's ever given.
天啊，我什么都没给你准备。
Gee, I didn't get you anything.
那些是他们吗?
Are those they?
不。
No.
这些都是菲多利的战利品。
These are entries into the Frito-Lay sweepstakes.
没有购买必要的。你想进来就进来，我也是。
No purchase necessary. Enter as often as you want, so I am.
太好了!多少次?
That's great! How many times?
这批是165万。
Well, this batch makes it 1,650,000.
我应该赢得32.6%的奖金，包括这辆车。
I should win 32.6% of the prizes, including the car.
这样就没什么意思了，不是吗?
That kind of takes the fun out of it, doesn't it?
但是他们制定了规则。
But they set up the rules.
我开始意识到我有一定的物质需求。
And I've come to realize I have certain materialistic needs.
所以,嗯…问题在哪里?
So, uh... Where are the questions?
我记住了他们。
I memorized them.
确定。
Sure.
嗯…我得去睡觉了。
Uh... I gotta go to sleep.
你想借我的睡衣吗?
Did you wanna borrow my pajamas?
不。不,谢谢。
No. No, thanks.
-嘿，他是个很聪明的孩子-是的。
- Hey, he's a pretty smart kid. - Yeah.
明年他就会长五英寸了。
He's gonna grow five inches in the next year.
——米奇?-乔丹?
- Mitch? - Jordan?
米奇·泰勒?
Mitch Taylor?
呃,谁……?
Uh, who...?
我叫雪莉·努吉尔。我等这一刻等了三年了。
My name is Sherry Nugil. I've been waiting three years for this.
——为了什么?-等你长大了。
- For what? - For you to be old enough.
——为了什么?- - - - - -。
- For what? - For this.
进来!
Come in!
哦,嗨,米奇!我只是在打磨地板!
Oh, hi, Mitch! I'm just sanding my floor!
你能把那个关了吗!
Could you turn that off a second?!
有什么事吗?你怎么出这么多汗?
What's the matter? How come you're so sweaty?
我帮完克里斯回来，发现我房间里有个女人。
I came back from helping Chris, and there was a woman in my room.
——原谅?——一个女人。你知道，她是个成年人。
- Pardon? - A woman. You know, she was an adult.
——哦。-她想…她想……-哦,上帝。我怎么能这么说呢?——你跳吗?
- Oh. - Well, she wanted... She wanted to... - Oh, God. How can I say this? - Jump you?
-是的。-你和她一起做的?
- Yeah. - You made it with her?
——没有。这是令人难以置信的。——原谅?
- No. That's what was unbelievable. - Pardon?
这是真的。我阻止了她。我告诉她我不想去。
It's true. I stopped her. I told her I didn't want to.
为什么?
Why?
因为我真的很想。
'Cause I really did want to.
——嗯?-我想。但是…没有和她在一起。
- Huh? - I wanted to. But... not with her.
哦。
Oh.
-这是我的上课时间。-今天是5月10日，杰里。
- This is my class hour. - It is the 10th of May, Jer.
——什么,唐?你在这里做什么?-我在做什么?
- What, Don? What are you doing here? - What am I doing--?
你在这里做什么?!
What are you doing here?!
你不知道，德克尔很危险!激光在哪里? !
You don't realize, Decker is dangerous! Where's the laser?!
——它的到来。-它甚至都没有呼吸困难。
- It's coming. - It's not even breathing hard.
杰瑞，他这周末就要激光!
Jerry, he wants the laser by the end of the week!
现在，你听我说!你匍匐的错误!
Now, you listen to me! You groveling bug!
我有考试!我已经尽力了，别再烦我了!
I have exams! I am doing what I can, so get off my back!
只要你保持冷静，那就差不多可以了。
Well, that should just about do the trick, as long as you stay cool.
-走吧，姑娘们。-你这是什么意思?
- Let's go, girls. - What do you mean by that?
这是一种比喻，鲍迪。你们到底来不来考试?
It's a figure of speech, Bodie. You guys coming to the exam or what?
我想是吧，因为海瑟薇为了生一个孩子费尽了心思。
I guess so, seeing as Hathaway's gone through all the trouble of having one.
你来吗，伙计?
You coming, buddy boy?
我一会儿就来找你们。我得去趟洗手间。
Uh, I'll catch up to you guys. I have to go to the bathroom.
好的,肯特。我觉得这对你的自信一点帮助都没有，对吧?
Okay, Kent. I don't think that's gonna help your confidence any, do you?
朋友的男孩。
Buddy boy.
看看你觉得这有多好笑。
Let's see how funny you think this is.
朋友的男孩。
Buddy boy.
好的,我们—
All right, we--
我们还有整整三个小时。
We have exactly three hours for this.
记住，同学们，我们这里信奉荣誉制度。
And remember, we believe in the honor system here, boys and girls.
不过很明显，你们中有多少人已经吸收了这些材料，有多少人没有。
Though it will be apparent to me how many of you have absorbed this material and how many of you haven't.
拿一个，传回去，就像你的智商正常一样。
Take one, pass it back, just like your IQ was normal.
祝你好运，伙计。
Good luck, buddy boy.
你介意我给第一个孩子取你的名字吗?
Do you mind if I name my first child after you?
"笨蛋骑士"听起来不错。
"Dipshit Knight" has a nice ring to it.
哇!
Whoa!
什么?
What?
不。不!
No. No!
不!
No!
不,不!
No, no!
我对你的崩溃表示哀悼，奈特。
My condolences on your meltdown, Knight.
肯特,什么危机?
What meltdown, Kent?
我不是说你有…因为我怎么知道?
I'm not saying that you had one... because how would I know?
但以防万一。
But just in case you do.
——你的粘液。-这是你自己的错，奈特
- You slime. - It's your own fault, Knight.
没人告诉过你要确保你的光学设备是干净的吗?
Didn't anyone ever tell you to make sure your optics are clean?
我能做到!被冻住是什么感觉!
I can do it! How does it feel to be frozen?!
是啊!冰很好!
Yeah! Ice is nice!
——Lazlo,伙计!你看到米奇了吗?——嗯…不。
- Lazlo, buddy! Have you seen Mitch? - Uh... No.
——不是吗?米奇!——没有。他不在里面。
- No? Mitch! - No. He's not in there.
-你怎么样?——如何?我通过了!但是我失败了!是啊!
- How'd you do? - How? I passed! But I failed! Yeah!
-那我又为你高兴又为你难过。——谢谢。
- Well, then I'm happy and sad for you. - Thank you.
要找到米奇。米奇!
Gotta find Mitch. Mitch!
这是美丽的。他不在厕所里。
That's beautiful. He's not in the toilet.
我要把它冷冻起来，至少得到一个数量级。
I'm gonna freeze it and get at least an order of magnitude.
因为它会被冻住。我想我能做到。
Because it's gonna be frozen. I think I can do it.
不确定。我得找到米奇。当心再见!
Not sure. I gotta find Mitch. Take care. Bye!
嘿,男人!你不是米奇。你也不是。
Hey, man! You're not Mitch. And you're not either.
嘿,Lazlo !想看重力的演示吗?是啊!
Hey, Lazlo! Wanna see a demonstration of gravity? Yeah!
-我一定要去!——克里斯!
- I gotta get there! - Chris!
这是可以做到的!这是一个窗口!那是一扇门!
It can be done! That's a window! That's a door!
这是一个大厅!
That's a hall!
是啊!米奇!你的数学在哪里? !
Yeah! Mitch! Where's your math?!
嘿,你混蛋!
Hey, you jerk!
-我很抱歉。-我给你买辆车。
- I'm very sorry. - I'll buy you a car.
我没有。这是我爸爸的。
I don't have one. It's my dad's.
米奇!
Mitch!
————什么?——嘿!最近怎么样，杰瑞?
- What the--? - Hey! How's it going, Jerry?
你想要什么，奈特?
What do you want, Knight?
世界和平。但我觉得现在不是讨论这个的时候。
World peace. But I don't think this is the time to discuss it.
——出去!-你可能会感兴趣，杰瑞。
- Get out! - Something might interest you, Jerry.
-你说什么我都不感兴趣。-海瑟薇博士…苏珊。
- I'm not interested in anything you say. - Dr. Hathaway... Susan.
我解决了电力问题，杰瑞。
I solved the power problem, Jerry.
杰里?
Jerry?
乘出租车。
Take a cab.
所以你以后再敲。
So you'll hammer later.
你也知道，米奇和我在研究氰化物系统。
As you know, Mitch and I were working on the cyanide system.
今天早些时候，它把自己吃掉了。
Well, earlier today, it ate itself.
但这正是我们向前迈出一大步所需要的。
But that's just what we needed to take a giant step forward.
肯特?
Right, Kent?
不用说，我对熔毁的事有点沮丧。
Needless to say, I was a little despondent about the meltdown.
但就在我准备哈利卡里的时候，我突然想到了。
But then, in the midst of my preparations for hari-kari, it came to me.
在氩基体中合成激发态溴是可能的。
It is possible to synthesize excited bromide in an argon matrix.
是的。它是一个处于激发态的准分子。
Yes. It's an excimer, frozen in its excited state.
这是不可能的。
That's impossible.
这是化学激光器。但是是固态的，不是气态的。
It's a chemical laser. But in solid, not gaseous form.
简而言之，为了尊重你，肯特，这就像发射一根炸药。
Put simply, in deference to you, Kent, it's like lasing a stick of dynamite.
只要我们施加一个场，我们就耦合到一个与地面辐射耦合的状态。
As soon as we apply a field, we couple to a state that is radiatively coupled to the ground.
我想我们可以每立方厘米提取10的21次方个质子，也就是每立方厘米在600纳米或者每升有1兆焦耳。
I figure we can extract 10-to-the-21st protons per cubic centimeter, which will give 1 kilojoule per cubic centimeter at 600 nanometers or 1 megajoule per liter.
那比太阳还热。
That's hotter than the sun.
——这是小。-它应该很小。
- It's small. - It's supposed to be small.
当然，我们只有一个样品…它会在激光的过程中自我毁灭。
Of course, we only have the one sample... and it's going to destroy itself as it lases.
但一切都会好起来的。
But everything's going to be fine.
-是吗，米奇?-是的。
- Isn't it, Mitch? - Yeah.
这完全是浪费时间。
This is a complete waste of time.
肯特，帮我个忙，把靶子放在煤渣砖前面，好吗?
Do me a favor, Kent, put the target in front of the cinder blocks, will you?
好的，到防护罩后面来。
Okay, come behind the shield.
-好的，泰勒先生。-随时准备好。
- Okay, Mr. Taylor. - Any time you're ready.
好的。
Okay.
准备好了吗?
Ready?
激光!
Laser on!
哇!
Whoa!
——太棒了!——好吧!
- Fantastic! - All right!
看看这个!
Look at this!
哇。
Wow.
-对不起，窗户坏了，先生。-还有院子对面的树!
- Sorry about the window, sir. - And the trees across the quad!
-多好的团队啊!——是的!
- What a team! - Yeah!
-你做到了。-我也做了我该做的。
- You did it. - I did my part too.
你毕业。你得到了这份工作。
You graduate. You get the job.
什么? !你不能!那是我的工作。
What?! You can't! That's my job.
你让我做的我都做了。你不能这么做!
I've done everything you've ever asked me to. You can't do this!
看!看!
Look! Look!
我替你上你的课!
I teach your classes for you!
-我帮你拿衣服!-他在做什么?
- I get your laundry! - What is he doing?
看,看。
Look, look.
我安装了目标跟踪系统的光学装置。
I mounted the optics for the target-tracking system.
现在看看这面镜子。
Now look at this mirror.
看!看!
Look! Look!
等待。等待。
Wait. Wait.
——让我们好好庆祝一下吧!——当然。
- Let's celebrate! - Absolutely.
你在校园里看到什么不寻常的东西了吗?
You see anything unusual on the campus?
——我的眼镜!-好吧，尽量别晃。
- My glasses! - Well, try not to wobble.
-有一个完整的洞。——这就是漂亮。
- There is a complete hole. - That's pretty.
看。
Look.
看那!
Look at that!
-我们去吃汉堡吧。- - - - - -来吧。
- Let's get a burger. - Come on.
——走吧!-什么，在里面?
- Let's go! - What, in there?
-这地方太狂野了。——什么?
- This place is wild. - What?
我可以把那些人打得落花流水。
I could clean those guys out at pool.
你看到了吗?
Do you see that?
你想见见她吗?她住在普拉亚德雷。
You wanna meet her? She lives in Playa del Rey.
-我会去见你父母吗?——没有。
- Am I gonna meet your parents? - No.
——为什么?你为我感到羞耻吗?——不,他们!
- Why? Are you ashamed of me? - No, them!
哦!
Oh!
你最好记住该感谢的人。
You better remember the right people to thank on this.
——听好了。我要感谢我的鱼。-什么意思?
- Listen up. I'd like to thank my fish. - What do you mean?
-还有Ikagami先生!-哦，我喜欢。
- And Mr. Ikagami! - Oh, I love it.
不，我说的是…
No, what I was talking about...
——这是,呃…-你想说什么?
- It's, uh... - What are you trying to say?
Lazlo。
Lazlo.
拉兹洛，我很高兴你出来了。你要一个汉堡包吗?
Lazlo, I'm so glad you came out. You want a hamburger?
我一直在考虑你的激光方案。
I've been thinking about your laser solution.
哦,很好。
Oh, good.
我想你已经把输出功率增加到6兆瓦了。
I figure you've increased the power output to 6 megawatts.
是的,。
Yeah, about that.
-你用它做什么?-做巨大的瑞士奶酪?
- What would you use that for? - Making enormous Swiss cheese?
应用是无限的。
The applications are unlimited.
不。用你想出来的燃料，光束能维持多久，15秒吧?
No. With the fuel you've come up with, the beam would last for what, 15 seconds?
-那有什么用?-拉兹洛，那不重要
- What good is that? - Oh, Lazlo, that doesn't matter.
我尊重你，但我已经毕业了。
I respect you, but I graduated.
让工程师们想办法利用它。这不关我们的事。
Let the engineers figure out a use for it. That's not our concern.
也许有人已经有了它的用途，它是专门为它设计的。
Maybe somebody already has a use for it, one for which it is specifically designed.
海瑟薇博士一直在想什么?
Dr. Hathaway had something in mind all along?
看看事实吧。
Look at the facts.
功率非常高，携带方便，发射时间有限，射程无限。
Very high power, portable, limited firing time, unlimited range.
你只需要一个跟踪系统和一个大旋转镜，你就可以从太空蒸发一个人类目标。
All you need is a tracking system and a large spinning mirror, and you could vaporize a human target from space.
这并不好。
This is not good.
不。
No.
发生了什么事?
What happened?
哦,不。
Oh, no.
——克里斯。-我没事。
- Chris. - I'm all right.
-他们拿走了一切。-肯特的追踪系统没了!
- They took everything. - Kent's tracking system's gone!
你怎么能造出那面镜子!
How could you build that mirror?!
他骗了我们。
He lied to us.
骗你很容易，米奇。
It's easy to lie to you, Mitch.
你信任的人。
You trust people.
我是一个愤世嫉俗者。
I'm a cynic.
我真是个混蛋。
I'm such an asshole.
我理解你的感受，克里斯。你是对的。
I understand how you feel, Chris. And you're right.
但我们现在应该做的是找出他在做什么。
But what we should be doing now is finding out what he's doing.
肯特。
Kent.
嘘!你们。
Shh! You guys.
-我们有两分钟时间。两分钟。——原谅?
- We'll have two minutes. Two minutes. - Pardon?
-嗨。-嗨。
- Hi. - Hi.
好了，张开他的嘴。
Okay, open his mouth.
好的。斗牛犬。
Okay. Bulldogs.
和收发器。
And transceiver.
和镊子。
And tweezers.
是牙套给了我灵感。
See, it was the braces that gave me the idea.
它们是完美的天线。他的整个脑袋变成了一个说话的人。
They're a perfect antennae. His whole head becomes a speaker.
是时候有人好好利用它了。
It's about time someone put it to good use.
肯特?
Kent?
肯特。醒来,肯特。
Kent. Wake up, Kent.
噢!
Ow!
-肯特!——什么?
- Kent! - What?
我在跟你说话，肯特。
I'm talking to you, Kent.
-这是什么?-我说了，我在和你说话。
- What is this? - I said, I'm talking to you.
——没有。-是的。
- No. - Yeah.
我没睡着。
Well, I'm not asleep.
-我一定是工作过度了。-你没有过度劳累，肯特。
- I must be overworked. - You're not overworked, Kent.
我又没疯!
Well, I'm not insane!
-我有吗?-那还有待观察，肯特
- Or am I? - That remains to be seen, Kent.
但我们正在谈话。
But we are having a conversation.
-你是谁?-这是耶稣，肯特。
- Okay, who is this? - This is Jesus, Kent.
你是一个非常淘气的孩子!
And you've been a very naughty boy!
好吧，你是谁?
All right, who is this?
-少废话，肯特你造了个武器。——什么?
- Cut the crap, Kent. You built a weapon. - What?
你以为秘密相位共轭跟踪系统是干什么用的?
What do you think a secret phase-conjugate tracking system is for?
大镜子形成大光束。
A big mirror makes a big beam.
我想可能是吧。
I guess it could be.
激光现在在哪里?
Where's the laser now?
我无意中听到杰瑞提到27号有个考试。
I overheard Jerry mention something about a test on the 27th.
但我不知道在哪里。这是机密。
But I don't know where. It's classified.
- - - - - -什么? !-哦，呃，没什么。
- What?! - Oh, uh, nothing.
我要你想想你做了什么，肯特。
I want you to think about what you've done, Kent.
从现在开始，别跟自己玩了!
And from now on, stop playing with yourself!
它是上帝。
It is God.
现在怎么办呢?
Now what?
第二阶段。
Phase two.
你是怎么回事?!
What is it with you?!
那是什么?
What's that?
-这些军人太不信任人了。-我们不能进入基地?
- These military people are so untrusting. - We can't get on-base clearance?
——我们将。-只需要6个小时
- We will. - It's just gonna take six hours.
算了吧。我们将球。
Forget it. We'll balls it.
这些看起来怎么样?
How do these look?
糟透了。我的像他，他的像我。
Terrible. Mine looks like him, and his looks like me.
太好了,我希望。
Great, I hope.
-如果这些骗不了任何人呢?-他们向我们开枪。
- What if these don't fool anybody? - They shoot us.
ID吗?
ID?
-把这些给下一个门的警卫看。——好的。你的赌注。
- Show these to the guard at the next gate. - Okey-doke. You bet.
id吗?
IDs?
嘿，你能把它收起来吗，伙计?我们刚飞过来。
Hey, can you snap it up, buddy? We just flew in.
我们迟到了，又累又饿，还租了辆破车。
We're late, we're tired, we're hungry, we rented this stupid car.
-你疯了吗?-你得恐吓他们。很酷。
- Are you out of your mind? - You gotta intimidate these guys. Be cool.
你不在名单上。
You're not on the list.
单吗?不在名单上。是啊，因为我们是机密。
List? Not on the list. Yeah, that's because we're classified.
是的。
Yeah.
安全。
Security.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
你们做技术员是不是太年轻了?
Aren't you guys a little young to be technicians?
激光是一门年轻的科学。
Lasers are a young science.
好的。好吧，是你逼我说的。现在我们都有麻烦了。
Okay. There, fine, you made me say it. Now we're both in trouble.
听着，我会打电话给值班警官。
Look, I'll call the duty officer.
——嗯…-你好，空降兵。
- Uh... - Hey there, uh, Airborne.
不要这样做。
Don't do that.
如果你打了电话，那就是我们的工作了。我们晚了四个小时。
If you make that call, it's our jobs. We're four hours late.
-是的，先生-让我们休息一下，好吗?
- Yes, sir. - Give us a break, will you, buddy?
也许有一天你也会在私营部门工作，对吧?
Someday you might be in the private sector too, right?
是的。
Yeah.
Yes.
——我们死了。-哦,不。
- We're dead. - Oh, no.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
——好的。-我喜欢。
- All right. - I love it.
当然,先生。
Absolutely, sir.
把它完成了。
Consider it done.
是的,先生。
Yes, sir.
-寻找任何不寻常的东西。——好的。
- Look for anything out of the ordinary. - Okay.
米奇。米奇,过来。
Mitch. Mitch, come here.
我的上帝。
My God.
好吧,来吧。
Okay, come on.
——板载内存?——检查。
- Onboard RAM? - Check.
-加载点处理器?——检查。
- Loading point processor? - Check.
DMA通道。
DMA channel.
激光控制系统。
Laser control system.
一级和二级激光探测系统全部启动。
Primary and secondary laser detection systems all go.
初级和次级激光激活系统全部启动。
Primary and secondary laser activation systems all go.
——处理器吗?——检查。
- Processor A? - Check.
- B处理器?——检查。
- Processor B? - Check.
——通信链路?——开放。
- Communications link? - Open.
-所有的诊断似乎都没问题。-最后的检查准备好了。
- All the diagnostics seem okay. - Final check ready.
65度，19分钟。
Sixty-five degrees, 19 minutes.
经度44度零9分。
Longitude 44 degrees, zero, 9 minutes.
-所有系统准备。-我们结束了，伙计们
- All systems go. - We're finished here, fellas.
什么? !
What?!
这个小多项式会让电脑忙到不知道我们在这里。
This little polynomial should keep the computer so busy, it doesn't even know we're here.
他们在哪儿?
Where are they?
-有联系。他们在!——哦!
- Got a connection. They're in! - Oh!
阿博特科斯特洛。
Abbott to Costello.
-我是科斯特洛。去做吧。-我们有好东西。
- This is Costello. Go ahead. - We've got the goodies.
我们已经计算出了目标坐标来进行轨迹调整。
We've got the target coordinates computed for trajectory adjustment.
收到，我们正在发送
Roger, we're sending.
——哦。——哦。
- Uh-oh. - Uh-oh.
它是什么?
What is it?
哦,没什么。
Oh, nothing.
你没想过我们会花这么多钱去太空测试吗?
You didn't think we'd blow all this money to test in space?
事实上，是的，我做了，因为这就是设计的目的。
Actually, yes, I did, because that is what it is designed for.
但如果以你的智慧，你觉得我们应该先学爬再学走，我是说，那也没关系。真的。
But if, in your wisdom, you feel we should learn to crawl before we walk, I mean, that's fine too. Really.
——注意!——什么?
- Attention! - What?
-上级长官来了!-就像你一样。
- Superior officer in the room! - As you were.
打扰一下。我们准备好进行最后的机载激光检查了。
Excuse me. We're ready for the final onboard laser check.
嘘!
Shh!
所有清晰。
All clear.
我要把PROM换成EPROM。
I'm replacing the PROM with our EPROM.
好吧,开枪。
Okay, shoot.
请告诉我坐标好吗?
May I have the coordinates, please?
北纬34度10分15秒21。
Thirty-four degrees, ten minutes, 15.21 seconds north.
190度，7分钟……
One hundred nineteen degrees, seven minutes...
这边走。
Right over this way.
我去检查楼梯。
I'm gonna check the stairs.
克里斯!海瑟薇的来了!
Chris! Hathaway's coming!
米奇刚刚通知我教授先生要来了。
Mitch has just informed me that Herr Professor is approaching.
-我们该怎么办?!-请快点。海瑟薇的到来。
- What do we do?! - Please hurry. Hathaway's coming.
请不要。我在压力下工作不好。
Please don't. I don't work well under pressure.
小心你的头。
Watch your head there.
我希望这样可以。
I hope that does it.
好吧，克里斯，我是说艾伯特。喂?喂?
Okay, Chris, I mean, Abbott. Hello? Hello?
他们跑了!
They're gone!
——好的。好吧。好吧。——好的。好吧。很好。
- Okay. Fine. Fine. - All right. Fine. Fine.
戈伊医生会为你解答你可能有的其他问题。
Dr. Goy here will explain any additional questions you might have.
是的。重复使用这个武器有什么问题吗?
Yes. Is there any problem with reusing the weapon?
不,没有问题。
No, no problem.
燃料被冷冻并包含在一个自给自足的单元中——每次使用后都是可更换的。——我明白了。
The fuel is frozen and contained within a self-sufficient unit - that's replaceable after each use. - I see.
这个系统的美妙之处在于燃料激光器…-这里一切都好吗?-为什么不呢?
The beauty of this system is that the fuel laser... - Is everything all right here? - Why shouldn't it be?
只要它还有效，我们就去。很好。
As long as it remains operative, we're going. Fine.
好吧，我想这差不多就是总结了。你不?嗯…我们该走了吗?
Well, I think that just about sums it up. Don't you? Uh... Shall we take our exit?
在我看来很小。
Looks small to me.
-好了，他们走了。-好险啊。
- Okay, they're gone. - That was close.
没有比借B-1更好的了，对吧，将军?
Nothing like borrowing a B-1, huh, general?
它是什么?
What is it?
什么都没有。
Nothing.
客观个人分析诊断精神分裂症…
Diagnosis of schizophrenia by objective personal analysis...
——嗨,肯特。——哦。
- Hi, Kent. - Oh.
我以为你已经走了。
I thought you'd gone.
还没有。你一直在摸自己吗?
Not yet. Have you been touching yourself?
是的。我的意思是,不!
Yes. I mean, no!
很好。听着,肯特。
Good. Listen, Kent.
爸爸，我爸爸，上帝，想给你看样东西。
Dad, you know, my father, God, wants to show you something.
为什么?我的意思是,什么?
Why? I meant, what?
我已经学会了不问。
I've learned not to ask.
他要你今天早上7点08分准时在艾维冠大道639号海瑟薇医生家门口等他。
He wants you to wait in front of Dr. Hathaway's house at 639 Ivy Crest Drive at precisely 7:08 this morning.
艾薇顶吗?
Ivy Crest?
就在那儿等着，你会收到信号的。
Just wait there and you shall receive a sign.
不要绝望，不要走进去。
Do not despair and do not go inside.
好吧,为什么不呢?
Well, why not?
喂?
Hello?
你好,耶稣吗?
Hello, Jesus?
他挂了电话。
He hung up.
弓弩一号，雷达发现，航向0-2-5。
Crossbow One, radar contact, take up a heading of 0-2-5.
爬升到飞行高度6-5-0。
Climb to maintain flight level 6-5-0.
收到。0-2-5，高度5000，飞行高度6-5-0。
Roger. We are 0-2-5 at a 5000 for flight level 6-5-0.
他们在这里。
They're here.
啊。奈特先生，为什么在这里见到你我一点都不惊讶?
Ah. Mr. Knight, why is it that I am not surprised to see you here?
我想你对我们将要见证的所谓事件有个解释吧。
And, uh, I suppose you have an explanation for this so-called event that we're to witness.
是的，先生，我知道。但首先，我要称赞你的时尚品味。
Yes, sir, I do. But first, let me compliment you on your fashion sense.
特别是你的拖鞋。
Particularly your slippers.
是啊，菲莱米娜喜欢。
Yes, well, uh, Fillamina likes them.
嘿,伙计们!
Hey, guys!
——克里斯。——早上好。
- Chris. - Good morning.
啊。国会议员Doogan。什么风把你吹来了?
Ah. Congressman Doogan. What brings you around?
我听说这里发生了一件非常重要的国际事件。
I was told there was a situation here of critical international importance.
所有武器功能都由这个模块控制，就像在太空中一样。
All weapon functions are controlled from this module, as it would be in space.
事实上，这是一模一样的汽车座舱。
In fact, this is an exact duplicate of the vehicle cockpit.
精度和功率将是精确的。
The accuracy and the power will be as exact.
-我们接近目标了。-开门。
- We are nearing the target. - Open the doors.
弩，打开炸弹舱门。
Crossbow, open bomb bay doors.
-那是非常严重的指控。-是的，先生，我知道
- Those are very serious accusations. - Yes, sir. I know.
如果是真的，我需要证据。
If it's true, I'm going to need proof.
我想我们可以在一分钟内给你们安排时间。
I think we can accommodate you both in just one minute.
鸭子。
Duck.
-哦，先生，下来。——国会议员?
- Oh, sir, down. - Congressman?
现在，你听我说，耶稣。
Now, you listen to me, Jesus.
这是杰瑞的房子…我们非常接近。
This is Jerry's house... and we're very close.
如果你不回答我，我就只能进去了。
So if you don't answer me, I'm just gonna have to go in.
-所以我要走了。——不,肯特!
- So I'm going. - No, Kent!
——离开!肯特!-别进去!
- Get away! Kent! - Don't go in there!
快离开那里!
Get away from there!
-别进去!-肯特!不!
- Don't go in there! - Kent! No!
肯特!
Kent!
目标锁定。十。
Target locked. In ten.
九个
Nine.
八个
Eight.
-肯特!-出来，肯特!
- Kent! - Come out, Kent!
好吧,上帝!给我吧!
Okay, God! Let me have it!
噢,瞧!
Oh, look!
爆米花。
Popcorn.
哦。
Oh.
不。
No.
我不明白你的意思。火吗?
I don't understand. Did it fire?
-开火了吗?-是的，但有个问题。
- Did it fire? - Yes, but there's a problem.
-它没有关闭。是的。-那就关掉它!
- It's not shutting down. Yes. - Well, shut it down!
-杰瑞，有什么问题吗?-关掉它!
- Jerry, what's the problem? - Shut it down!
肯特。
Kent.
哟!
Whee!
——啊!-肯特。
- Whee! - Kent.
-肯特!——嗨,肯特!
- Kent! - Hey, Kent!
-肯特!-肯特?
- Kent! - Kent?
-肯特，你没事吧?-太棒了!
- Kent, you okay? - That was great!
——收到，一号。-出事了。
- Roger, one. - Something is very wrong.
出去!
Out!
解开鸟瞰图。
Unlock the bird's-eye.
解锁。
Unlocked.
我在追踪子弹的去向。
I'm tracking where the shot went.
我想知道它是否有效。
I want to know it worked.
加油！加油
Come on, come on.
——什么?
What the--?
哦,不。
Oh, no.
——我的房子。-你做了什么?
- My house. - What have you done?
好吧!
All right!
-看那个角落!——太好了。
- Look at the corner! - That's great.
霍利菲尔德开着温尼贝戈!
It's Hollyfeld in a Winnebago!
Lazlo,老兄!
Lazlo, buddy!
我想我们用得太多了。
I think we used too much.
-很遗憾你错过了。-是的。我得收拾行李。
- I'm sorry you missed it. - Yeah. Well, I had to pack.
——为什么?-我要结婚了。
- Why? - I'm getting married.
——谁?-这些都是什么?
- To whom? - What is all this stuff?
哦,是的。
Oh, yeah.
我赢了，31.8%的奖金。
I won, 31.8% of the prizes.
我得想办法。但今年夏天不是。
I'll have to figure that out. But not this summer.
-嗨。——雪莉?
- Hi. - Sherry?
雪莉Nugil吗?
Sherry Nugil?
-很棒吧?-这是第一个。
- Isn't it great? - This is number one.
我找他找了十年了。
I've been looking for him for ten years.
-我能说什么呢?她爱我。——恭喜你。
- What can I say? She loves me. - Congratulations.
好的。
Okay.
-你一定要来看看我们。-什么意思?
- You'll have to come and visit us. - What do you mean?
我在怀俄明州有个小小的求生之所。我们要住在那里。
I have a little survival place in Wyoming. We're gonna live there.
是啊，这里越来越奇怪了，你知道吗?
Yeah, it's getting kind of weird around here, you know?
——再见。——再见。
- Bye. - Bye.
再见。
Goodbye.
你觉得这里太奇怪了吗?
Think it's getting too weird around here?
绝对的。
Absolutely.
-我没注意到。-我喜欢。
- I didn't notice. - I like it.
♬欢迎来到你的生活
♪ Welcome to your life ♪
♪没有回头路♪
♪ There's no turning back ♪
即使在我们睡觉的时候
♪ Even while we sleep ♪
♬我们会找到你按你最好的行为♬
♪ We will find you Acting on your best behavior ♪
♪背弃自然妈妈♪
♪ Turn your back on Mother Nature ♪
每个人都想统治世界
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
♬那是我自己的愿望
♪ It's my own desire ♪
这是我自己的悔恨
♪ It's my own remorse ♪
帮我决定
♪ Help me to decide ♪
♪帮助我充分享受自由和快乐♪
♪ Help me make the most of freedom And of pleasure ♪
没有什么是永恒的
♪ Nothing ever lasts forever ♪
每个人都想统治世界
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
♬有一个房间，在那里阳光不会找到你♬
♪ There's a room Where the light won't find you ♪
♪牵手，当墙倒塌♪
♪ Holding hands While the walls come tumbling down ♪
当他们找到我的时候，我就在你身后
♪ When they do, I'll be right behind you ♪
真高兴我们快到了
♪ So glad we've almost made it ♪
♪太悲伤了，他们不得不让它褪色
♪ So sad they had to fade it ♪
每个人都想统治世界
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
我无法忍受这种优柔寡断
♪ I can't stand this indecision ♪
♬嫁给了一个缺乏远见的人♬
♪ Married with a lack of vision ♪
每个人都想统治世界
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
♪说你永远，永远永远都不需要它
♪ Say that you'll never, never Never need it ♪
♬一个标题，为什么要相信?♪
♪ One headline, why believe it? ♪
每个人都想统治世界
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
我无法忍受这种优柔寡断
♪ I can't stand this indecision ♪
♬嫁给了一个缺乏远见的人♬
♪ Married with a lack of vision ♪
每个人都想统治世界
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
♪说你永远，永远永远都不需要它
♪ Say that you'll never, never Never need it ♪
♬一个标题，为什么要相信?♪
♪ One headline, why believe it? ♪
每个人都想统治世界
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪
♬一切为了自由和快乐
♪ All for freedom and for pleasure ♪
没有什么是永恒的
♪ Nothing ever lasts forever ♪
每个人都想统治世界
♪ Everybody wants to rule the world ♪